  - Can't Knock The Hustle
"Can't Knock The Hustle"(feat. Mary J. Blige)  I'm making short term goals, wonder whether foes just put away the leathers and put ice on the gold chilly with enough bail money to free a big Willy high stakes, I got more at stake than Philly shopping sprees, coping three, deuce fever I guess its fully loaded, ah yes, bouncing in the lex luger, tires smoke like Buddha 50 g's to the crap shooter, niggas can't fade me chrome socks beaming, through my peripheral I see ya scheming stop dreamin', I leave ya body steaming niggas is feening, what's the meaning I'm leaning on any nigga intervening with the sound of my money machine-in my cuff running over with hundreds I'm one of the best niggas that done it six digits and running, y'all niggas don't want it I got the godfather flow, the don Juan Demarco swear to god, don't get it fucked up[Chorus - Mary J. Blige] taking out this time to give you a piece of my mind (cause you can't knock the hustle) but though you think you are baby one day you'll be a star last seen out of state where I drop my slang I'm deep in the south kicking up top game bouncing on the highway switching 4 lanes screaming through the sun roof money ain't a thang your worst fear confirmed, me and my fam roll tight like the firm getting down for life, that's right, you better learn why play with fire, burn we get together like a choir to acquire what we desire we do dirt like worms produce g's like sperm 'til legs spread like germs I got extensive hoes, with expensive clothes and I sip wine, and spit vintage flows but y'all don't know...... yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, cause you can't knock the hustle[Mary J. Blige:] but until that day then I'm the one whose crazy cause that's the way ya making me feel (cause you can't knock the hustle) I'm just trying to get mine, I don't have the time to knock the hustle for real y'all niggas lunching, punching a clock my function is lo make much 'n' lay back munching sipping Remy on rocks, my crew something to watch nothing to stop un... ...stoppable scheme on the ice, I gotta hide your crew I gotta let you niggas know the time like movado my motto, stack rocks like Colorado bottle off the champagne, crystals by the bottle it's a damn shame what you're not though (who?) me slick like a GATO fuckin'  pops knew exactly what he did when he made me tried to get a nut and he got a nut and what straight banana's can a nigga, see me got the US Open, advantage jigga serve like sampras, play fake a rappers like a campus Le Tigre, son you're too eager you ain't having it? good, me either lets get together and make this whole world believers at my arraignment, screaming all these blacks got is sports and entertainment, until we even thieving, as long as I'm breathing can't knock the way a nigga eating fuck you even[Mary J. Blige:] taking out this time to give you a piece of my mind but though you think you are baby one day you'll be a star but until that day then I'm the one whose crazy cause that's the way ya making me feel, I'm just trying to get mine, I don't have the time to knock the hustle for real  
  - Politics As Usual
"Politics As Usual"  You know how we do, Roc-a-Fella... forever... You can catch me skatin through your town puttin it down y'all relatin No waitin I'll make your block infrared hot I'm like Satan Y'all feel a nigga's struggle, y'all think a nigga love to hustle behind the wheel, tryin to escape my trouble kids stop they greetin me, I'm talkin sweet to keys Cursin the very God, that bought this wreath to be My life is, based on sacrifices, jewels like ices and fools that think I slip, you fuck around you get your guys hit, they built me to be filthy on some I-do-or-die shit, for real The price of leather's got me, deeper than ever and just think, with this here, I'm tryin to feel made nig-ga Politics as us-ual... I took my Frito to Tito in the district, blessed me with some VS somethins I can live with, stop frontin And for the dough I raise, gotta get shit appraised No disrespect to you, make sure you word is true I'm takin wages down in Vegas just in case Tyson have a major night off, that's clean money, the tax write-off You ain't seen money in your life, when it comes to this cheese y'all like Three Blind Mice A smokin bro, who pump Willie Ike spokes The furthest you Chiles been is the Pocanos My portfolio reads: leads to Don Corleone, nigga please Ten year feleon, heavy on the wrist, our face used with the diamond blooded Jesus and blind your face youse for life... sharight, Jigga, I keep it tight nig-ga Politics as us-ual... You feel my triumph never, feel my pain I'm lyin Low in the leather Zion, the best that's ever came The game changes like, my mind just ain't right We 'gwan get this dough, I guess it ain't your night Suckin me in like a vacumn, I remember tellin my family I'll be back soon, that was December Eighty-five and,  rise ten years later got me wise still can't break my underworld ties I wear black a lot, in the Ac', act a lot Got matchin VCR's, a huge Magnavox to nitch, green like spinach pop wines that's vintage It's a lot of big money in my sentence Hittin towards a mil', lip a, written I kill like that chick faked me one-two cat, yeah, I do dat Ain't no stoppin the champagne from poppin the drawers from droppin, the law from watchin, I hate em Politics as us-ual     
  - Brooklyn's Finest
"Brooklyn's Finest"(feat. Notorious B.I.G.)[Pain In Da Ass][gunshots] OKAY, I'M RELOADED!!!  You motherfuckers, think you big time?  Fuckin with , you gon' die, big time! Here come the "Pain"! [gunshots][] Jigga... (Jigga), Bigga... (Bigga) Nigga, how you figure... (how you figure) Yeah, yeah, yeah, aiyyo Peep the style and the way the cops sweat us (uh-huh) The number one question is can the Feds get us (uh-huh) I got vendettas in dice games against ass betters (uh-huh) and niggaz who pump wheels and drive Jettas Take that witcha..[Notorious B.I.G.] .. hit ya, back split ya Fuck fist fights and lame scuffles Pillow case to your face, make the shell muffle Shoot your daughter in the calf muscle Fuck a tussle, nickel-plated  Sprinkle coke on the floor, make it drug related Most hate it..[] .. can't fade it While y'all pump Willie, I run up in stunts silly Scared, so you sent your little mans to come kill me  But on the contrilli, I packs the mack-milli  Squeezed off on him, left them paramedics breathin soft on him  What's ya name?[Notorious B.I.G.] .. Who shot ya? Mob ties like Sinatra Peruvians tried to do me in, I ain't paid them yet Tryin to push 700's, they ain't made them yet Rolex and bracelets is frostbit; rings too Niggaz 'round the way call me Igloo Stix (Who?) Motherfucker![Chorus]  and Biggie Smalls, nigga shit ya drawers (Where you from?) Brooklyn, goin out for all Marcy - that's right - you don't stop Bed-Stuy.. you won't stop, nigga![] What, what, what? , Big' Smalls, nigga shit ya drawers Brooklyn represent y'all, hit you fold You crazy, think your little bit of rhymes can play me? I'm from Marcy, I'm varsity, chump, you're JV (Jigga) [Notorious B.I.G.] .. and Bigga baby! My Bed-Stuy flow's malicious, delicious Fuck three wishes, made my road to riches from 62's, gem stars, my moms dishes Gram choppin, police van dockin D's at my doors knockin[] What? Keep rockin No more, Mister, Nice Guy, I twist your shit  the fuck back with them pistols, blazin Hot like cajun Hotter than even holdin work at the Days Inn with New York plates outside Get up outta there, fuck your ride[Notorious B.I.G.] Keep your hands high, shit gets steeper Here comes the Grim Reaper, Frank Wright Leave the keys to your In-tegra (That's right) Chill homie, the bitch in the Shoney's told me You're holdin more drugs than a pharmacy, you ain't harmin me So pardon me, pass the safe, before I blaze the place  and here's six shots just in case (Brooklyn... Brooklyn... Brooklyn...)[Chorus]  and Biggie Smalls, nigga shit ya drawers (Where you from?) Brooklyn goin out to all (Crown Heights...) You don't stop (Brownsville...) You won't stop, nigga! (Brooklyn... Brooklyn... Brooklyn...) Hah hah!  and Biggie Smalls, nigga shit ya drawers (Where we from?) Brooklyn goin out to all (Bushwick...) You don't stop (Fort Greene...) You won't stop, niggaz![] Yeah, yeah, yeah For nine six, the only MC with a flu Yeah I rhyme sick, I be what you're tryin to do Made a fortune off Peru, extradite, china white heron Nigga please, like short sleeves I bear arms Stay out my way from here on (CLEAR?) Gone![Notoriuos B.I.G.] Me and Gutter had two spots The two for five dollar hits, the blue tops Gotta go, Coolio mean it's gettin "Too Hot" If Fay' had twins, she'd probably have two-Pac's Get it? .. Tu-pac's[] Time to separate the pros from the cons The platinum from the bronze That butter soft shit from that leather on the Fonz A S1 diamond from a eye class don A Cham' Dom' sipper from a Rosay nigga, huh?! Brook-Nam, sippin on [Notorious B.I.G.] Cristal forever, play the crib when it's mink weather The M.A.F.I.A. keep canons in they Marc Buchanans Usually cuatro cinco, the shell sink slow, tossin ya Mad slugs through your Nautica, I'm warnin ya (Hah, what the fuck?)[Chorus]  and Biggie Smalls, nigga shit ya drawers (Where you from?) Brooklyn goin out to all (Flatbush...) You don't stop (Redhook...) You won't stop, nigga! (Brooklyn... Brooklyn... Brooklyn...)  and Biggie Smalls, nigga shit ya drawers (Where you from?) Brooklyn goin out to all (East New York...) You don't stop (Clinton Hill...) You won't stop, nigga! ("Is Brooklyn in the house?")[Outro] Uhh, Roc-A-Fella, y'all, Junior M.A.F.I.A.  Superbad click, Brook-lyn's Finest, you re-wind this  Represetin BK to the fullest     
  - Dead Presidents
"Dead Presidents II"[Chorus:] "Presidents to represent me" - [Nas] "Get money!" "I'm out for presidents to represent me" "Get money!" "I'm out for presidents to represent me" "Get money!" "I'm out for dead *fuckin* presidents to represent me (Whose...)" Rock... on, Roc-A-Fella y'all The saga continues Ahh, who wanna bet us that we don't touch leathers Stack cheddars forever, live treacherous all the et ceteras To the death of us, me and my confidants, we shine You feel the ambiance, y'all niggaz just rhyme By the ounce dough accumulates like snow We don't just shine, we illuminate the whole show; you feel me? Factions from the other side would love to kill me Spill three quarts of my blood into the street, let alone the heat Fuck em, we hate a nigga lovin this life In all possible ways, know the Feds is buggin my life Hospital days, reflectin when my man laid up On the Uptown high block he got his side sprayed up I saw his life slippin, this is a minor set back Yo, still in all we livin, just dream about the get back That made him smile though his eyes said, "Pray for me" I'll do you one better and slay these niggaz faithfully Murder is a tough thing to digest, it's a slow process and I ain't got nothin but time I had near brushes, not to mention three shots close range, never touched me, divine intervention Can't stop I, from drinkin Mai-Tai's, with Ta Ta Down in Nevada, ha ha, Poppa, word life I dabbled in crazy weight without rap, I was crazy straight Potnah, I'm still spendin money from eighty-eight... what?[Chorus] Geyeah, know what? I'll make.. you and your wack mans fold like bad hands Roll like Monopoly, ad-vance you copy me like white crystals, I gross the most at the end of the fiscal year than these niggaz can wish to The dead presidential, canidate with the sprinkles and the presidental, ice that'll offend you In due time when crime fleas my mind All sneak thieves and playa haters can shine But until then I keep the trillion cut diamonds shinin brilliant I'll tell you half the story, the rest you fill it in Long as the villian win I spend Japan yen, attend major events Catch me in the joints, convinced my iguanas is bitin J-A-Y hyphen, controllin, manipulatin I got a good life man, pounds and pence Nuff dollars make sense, while you ride the bench Catch me swinging for the fence Dead Presidents, ya know[Chorus] Uh-huh, yeah, uh-huh, so be it The Soviet, The Unified Steady Flow You already know, you light I'm heavy roll, heavy dough Mic macheted your flow, your paper falls slow like confetti, mines a steady grow, bet he glow Pay five dead it from blow, better believe I have eleven sixty to show, my doe flip like Tae-Kwon  The Icon, baby, you like Dom, maybe this Cristal's to change your life huh, roll with the winners Heavy spenders like hit records: Roc-A-Fella Don't get it corrected this shit is perfected  from chips to chicks just drivin a Lexus Make it without your gun, we takin everything you brung We cake and you niggaz is fake and we gettin it done Crime Family, well connected  And you fake thugs is Unplugged like MTV I empty three, take your treasure, my pleasure Dead presidentials, politics as usual Bla-ouw! "Dead (fuckin) presidents to represent me (Whose...)" "Dead (fuckin) presidents to represent me (Whose...)" "Dead (fuckin) presidents to represent me (Whose...)" "Dead (fuckin) presidents to represent me (Whose...)"[Chorus 2X]    
  - Feelin It
"Feelin It"[Chorus:] I'm feelin it fill the glass to the top with Moet Feelin it feel the Lex pushin up on the set I'm feelin it through the high that you get from the lie Feelin it if you feel it raise your l in the sky[Verse 1:] I keep it realer than most I know your feelin it Cristal on ice I like to toast I keep on spillin it Bone crushers I keep real close I got the skill for this On my back the fliest clothes lookin ill and shit Transactions illegitimate cause life is still a bitch  And then you die but for now life close your eyes and feel this dick Since diapers had nothin to live for like them lifers but  Makin sure every nigga stay rich within my cipher We paid the price to circular success they turned my mic up I'm 'bout to hit these niggas wit some shit that a light they life up If every nigga in your clique is rich your clique is rugged Nobody will fall cause everyone would be each others crutches  I hope you fools choose to listen I drop jewels bust it These are the rules I follow in my life you gotta love it Jiggy jigger lookin gully in the joint  If y'all niggas ain't talkin 'bout large money what's the point?[Chorus][Verse 2:] Even if it ain't sunny hey I ain't complainin  I'm in the rain doing a buck 40 hydroplanin what shorty (Where you disappear son?) Maintainin puttin myself in a position most of these rappers ain't in I'm livin the ill streets blues got you hunger painin Nothin to gain and a whole lot to lose you still singin fool I'm thorough in every boro my name be ringin Warmin it up for the perfect time to hit your brain and  Ya Feelin it? to all the girls I bought the girdle to conceal my bricks No doubt they can vouch my life is real as shit  95 south and poppy on the hill and shit And all the towns like Cambridge that I killed wit shit And all the thorough ass niggas that I hustle wit  Throw your joints in the air one time and bust your shit These fake rappers cant really know I'm lovin it ya feelin it[Chorus x2][Verse 3:] What y'all ain't heard that nigga Jay high?  The Cristals they keep me wet like Baywatch I keep it tight for all the nights my mom prayed I'd stop  Said she had dreams that snipers hit me with a fatal shot Those nightmares mom Those dreams you say you got give me the chills But these mils make me hot y'all feel me Enough to stop the illin right? But at the same time these dimes keep me feelin tight  I'm so confused OK I'm gettin weeded now I know I'm contradicting myself Look I don't need that now  It just once in a blue moon when there's nothin to do and The tension's too thick for my sober mind to cut through I get to zonin, me and the chick on the island and we're bonin' I free my mind sometimes I here myself moanin Take one more toke and I leave that weed alone man It got me goin shit[Chorus x3] 
  - D'Evils
"D'Evils"  Dear God, I wonder can you save me? Illuminati want my mind, soul, and my body. Dear God, I wonder can you save me? Secret Society, Tryin to keep their eye on me Dear God, I wonder can you save me? Illuminati want my mind, soul, and my body. Dear God, I wonder can you save me? I can't Die, I can't Die, I can't Die [echoes fade] (Uh, yeah) This shit is wicked on these mean streets None of my friends speak We're all trying to win, but then again Maybe it's for the best though, 'cause when your're saying too much You know they're trying to get you touched Whoever said illegal was the easy way out couldn't understand the mechanics And the workings of the underworld, granted Nine to five is how ya survive, I ain't trying to survive I'm trying to live it to the limit and love it alive Life ills, poison my body I used to say 'fuck mic skills, ' and never prayed to God, I prayed to Gotti That's right it's wicked, west life I live it Ain't asking for forgiveness for my sins, endz I break bread with the late heads, picking their brains for angles on All the evils that the game'll do It gets dangerous, money and power is changing us And now we're lethal, infected with D'Evils... Dear God, I wonder can you save me? Illuminati want my mind, soul, and my body. Dear God, I wonder can you save me? Secret Society, Tryin to keep their eye on me Dear God, I wonder can you save me? Illuminati want my mind, soul, and my body. Dear God, I wonder can you save me? I can't Die, I can't Die, I can't Die [echoes fade] (Yeah, yeah) We used to fight for building blocks Now we fight for blocks with buildings that make a killing The closest of friends when we first started But grew apart as the money grew, and soon grew black-hearted Thinking back when we first learned to use rubbers He never learned so in turn I'm kidnapping his baby's mother My hand around her collar, feeding her cheese She said the taste of dollars was shitty so I fed her fifties About his whereabouts I wasn't convinced So I kept feeding her money 'til her shit started to make sense Who could ever forsee, we used to stay up all night at slumber parties Now I'm trying to rock this bitch to sleep All the years we were real close Now I see his fears through her tears, know she's wishing we were still close Don't cry, it is to be In time, I'll take away your miseries and make 'em mine, D'Evils... Dear God, I wonder can you save me? Illuminati want my mind, soul, and my body. Dear God, I wonder can you save me? Secret Society, Tryin to keep their eye on me Dear God, I wonder can you save me? Illuminati want my mind, soul, and my body. Dear God, I wonder can you save me? I can't Die, I can't Die, I can't Die [echoes fade] (Yeah) My flesh, no nigga could test My soul is possessed by D'Evils in the form of diamonds and lexuses The exorcist, got me doing skits like Homie You don't know me, but the whole world owe me Strip! Was thought to be a pleasant guy all my fucking life So now I'm down for whatever, ain't nothing nice Throughout my junior high years it was all friendly But now this higher learning got the Remy in me Liquors invaded my kidneys Got me ready to lick off, mama forgive me I can't be held accountable, D'Evils beating me down, boo Got me running with guys, making G's, telling lies that sound true Come test me, I never cower For the love of money, son, I'm giving lead showers Stop screaming, you know the demon said it's best to die And even if Jehovah witness, bet he'll never testify, D'Evils... Dear God, I wonder can you save me? I can't Die, I can't Die, I can't Die [echoes fade][Disc scratch and fade] 
  - 22 Two's
"22 Two's"[people clapping] Yo whassup everybody this is Mariah Davis, Mad Wednesday's we here tonight to have a good time ("Yo! Start the show! Start the show!") Wait a minute; I see my man over there  , Dam Deass let me hear that lil' tape of yours, and it's fat Why don't you come up here and kick a lil' freestyle Put that champagne down, and kick a lil' freestyle for me tonight[] Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah Can I kick it? (Yes you can!) [repeat 3X] Y'all motherfuckers musta hear that Tribe Called Quest, let's do it again Can I kick it? (Yes you can!) [repeat 3X] Well I'm gone... check this out Too much West coast dick-lickin, and too many niggaz on a mission Doin your best  rendition Too many rough motherfuckers, I got my suspicions that you're just a fish in a pool of sharks nigga, listen Too many bitches wanna be ladies, so if you a hoe I'ma call you a hoe, too many bitches are shady Too many ladies give these niggaz too many chances Too many brothers wannabe lovers don't know what romance is Too many bitches stuck up from too many sexual advances No question;  got too many answers I been around this block, too many times Rocked, too many rhymes, cocked, too many nines, too To all my brothers it ain't too late to come together Cause too much black and too much love, equal forever I don't follow any guidelines cause too many niggaz ride mine so I change styles every two rhymes, hah, what the fuck That's 22 too's for y'all motherfuckers out there, yaknahmean? Shall I continue? Check it out, what? Can I kick it? (Yes you can!) [repeat 3X] Well I'm gone... yo, yo, yo Copped to reach my quota, push rock, roll up smooth like on ya Whole groove like hold-up, swoll up Too many faggot niggaz, clockin my spendin Exercisin you're, gay like minds like Richard Simmons If you could catch Jay right, on the late night without the eight right, maybe you could test my weight, right I dip, speak quicker than you ever seen adminster pain, next the minister's screamin your name At your wake as I peak in, look in your casket feelin sarcastic, "Look at him, still sleepin" You never ready, forever petty minds stay petty Mines thinkin longevity until I'm seventy Livin heavenly, fuck, felony after felony, what? Nigga ya broke, what the fuck you gon' tell me? ("Oooooooooooh!") , , now you know this is a fat track (aight) Now this is comin on your new album, on Roc-A-Fella records in ninety-six (no doubt no doubt) well, it is definitely the bomb But you know I do wanna say somethin to you, I know you've been havin a lot of problems with the law But I know you innocent, and I'm behind you 100% Mad Wednesday's, Ruby King, DJ Ace, Dang Dash Roc-A-Fella Records, we all behind you, you can come back anytime (Hah, thanks a lot) Wait a minute wait a minute wait a minute wait a minute Ace, turn that music down I smell some reefer, now you see? That's why, our people don't have anything Because we don't know how to go in places and act properly ("Hey shut the fuck up!") Wait a minute wait a minute who told me shut the eff up? Who told me to shut the eff up? Get him out of here I'm not gonna continue this show, until you throw him out Get him out right now, then I'ma continue my speech Thank you, he's out of here now, now like I was sayin We gotta build our own business, we gotta get our own record companies goin like Roc-A-Fella Records...     
  - Can I Live
"Can I Live"  Yeah, hah, yeah Roc-A-Fella We invite you to, somethin epic y'all know? Where we hustle out of a sense of hopelessness Sort of a desperation Through that desperation, we 'come addicted Sorta like the fiends we accustomed to servin But we feel we have nothin to lose So we offer you, well, we offer our lives, What do you bring to the table? While I'm watchin every nigga watchin me closely My shit is butter for the bread they wanna toast me I keep my head, both of them where they supposed to be Hoes'll get you sidetracked then clapped from close feet I don't sleep, I'm tired, I feel wired like codeine, these days A brother gotta admire me from four fiends away My pain wish it was quick to see, from sellin 'caine Til brains was fried to a fricaisse, can't lie At the time it never bothered me, at the bar Gettin my thug on properly, my squad and me Lack of respect for authority, laughin hard Happy to be escapin poverty, however brief I know this game got valleys and peaks, expectation For dips, for precipitation we stack chips, hardly The youth I used to be, soon to see a mill' in No more, Big Willie my game has grown prefer you call me William Illin for revenues, Rayful Edmonds like Channel 7 news, round seven jewels, hand gettin the mic Forgettin all I ever knew, convenient amnesia I suggest you call my lawyer, I know the procedure Lock my body can't trap my mind, easily Explain why we adapt to crime I'd rather die enormous than live dormant that's how we on it Live at the main event, I bet a trip to Maui on it Presidential suites my residential for the weekend Confidentially speakin in codes since I sense you peekin The NSX rental, don't be fooled my game is mental We both ride our town dog, what you tryin to get into? Viva, Las Vegas, see ya, later at the crap tables Meet me by the one that starts a G up This way no fraud Willie's present gambling they re-up And we can have a pleasant time, sippin margaritas Ge-ge-geyeahhh, can I live? Can I live? My mind is infested, with sick thoughts that circle Like a Lexus, if driven wrong it's sure to hurt you Dual level like duplexes, in unity, my crew and me Commit atrocities like we got immunity You guessed it, manifest it intangible goods Platinum Rolexed it, we don't lease We buy the whole car, as you should My confederation, dead a nation, EXPLODE On detonation, overload the mind of a said patient When it boils to steam, it comes to it We all fiends gotta do it, even righteous minds go through this True this, the streets school us to spend our money foolish Bond with jewelers and, watch for intruders I stepped it up another level, meditated like a buddhist Recruited lieutenants with ludicrous, dreams of Gettin cream let's do this, it gets te-di-ous So I keep one eye open like, C-B-S, ya see me Stressed right? Can I live? Can I live? Can I live? Can I live? Ha-hah, Roc-A-Fella y'all  
  - Ain't No Nigga
"Ain't No Nigga"(feat. Foxy Brown)[] I keep it fresher than the next bitch no need..for you to ever sweat the next bitch ..with speed, I make the best bitch see the exit..indeed,  you gotta know your thoroughly respected by me, you get the keys to the Lexus, with no driver you gotcha own '96 suh-in..the ride and keep your ass tighter than Versace thats why you gotta watch your friends you got to watch me they conniving shit the first chance to crack the bank they try me, all they get is 50 cent franks and papayas, from the village to the tele time to kill it on your belly no question  I got more black chicks between my sheets than Essence they say sex is a weapon, so when I shoot mmet your death in less than 8 seconds still poundin in my after life.. laugin my shit is tight you who askin right...[Chorus:] Aint no nigga like the one I got no one can fuck you betta sleeps around but he gives me alot keeps you in diamonds and leathers friends 'ill tell me I should leave you alone hah hah, hah hah, hah hah, hah ha tell the freaks to find a man of there own (man a they own, man a they own)[] Fresh to def in Moschino, coach bag lookin half black and filipino fakin no jacks got you a beeper to feel important surrouding your feet in Joanie Dega's and Charles Jordan I keep ya dove but love  you know these ho's be makin me weak yall knows how it goes 'b and so I creep Ive been sinnin since you been playin wit Barbie and Ken in you can't change a players game in the 9th inning the chrome rim spinning keeps em grinnin so I run way the fuck up in em and wrinkle the face like linnin I play hard-eh till they say God.. he's keepin it real jigga stay hard lawd don't even trip I never slip, nigga what you dont see is whatcha get weapons concealed what the fuck yall feel when you nigga play sick we can all get ill -whats the deal-[Chorus][] Yo, aint no stoppin this, no lie promise to stay monogamous, I try but love you know these ho's be makin me weak Y'all knows how it goes B so I stay deep[Foxy Brown] What up boo just keep me laced in the illa snakes bank rolls and shit, back rubs in the french tubs Mackin this bitch, wifee nigga  so when you flip that coke  remember them days you was dead broke but now your style and I raised you basically made you into a don flippin weight..heroin and shit you know my pussy is all that thats why I get bagets 5 carats and all that From Dolce Gabana to H Vendell I'm ringin bells so who the playa, I still keep you in the illest gators Tailor made so we can lay up in the shade reminiscin on how I fuck the best a shit specially when Im flippin Baileys dont give a fuck about how you move with them other mamis I push da Z, eating shrimp scampi with rocks larger than life Fuck them Reebok broads, you made it known who your wife was I got you frontin in Armani sweaters before this rap shit  when you was in letters and bullshit berattas and eek classes with mo in the glasses shows in Cali wit all the flavor suede Bally's now all your mens' up in your benz's high post, I swear you be killin me playin inside my pubic hairs I never worry bout them other chicks cuz you proved who was your wiz when you was spinnin that bitch I took a little when you was up north your comisary stay pilin how you livin large on the island all them collects have me vex but when you come home  knew I was comin off wit half of dem checks now we on the rise your diamond mami wit the slanted eyes holdin this grip cocked the green and the shit Fucks no, I see half the dough Made you into a star, pushin hundred thousand dollar cars[Chorus]    
  - Friend Or Foe
"Friend Or Foe"  Check one check two, you know what to do Primo, cold crush when I give it to you Friend or foe yo, state your biz Ya tend to dough, ah, there it is Me, I run the show, oh, and these kids Don't like nobody commin around here fuckin wit they doe for shit You enterprisin though, And I like it But fuck with the big dogs though, I gotta bite ya, Look, its out of my hands And you gettin money round here, its not in the plans So hop yo ass out of that van, head back to kansas I'm sendin niggas back up in campuses Chance is slimmer than that chick in calvin klien pantses Let me guess, they said it was money round here And the rest is me stoppin you from gettin it, correct? Sorry to hear that, my guess is you got work at the hotel I'll take care of that, you'll see, now please Give me the room key You're twitchin, don't do that, you makin me nervous My crew, well, they do pack, them niggas is murderous So would ya, please put your hand back in sight They don't like to see me nervous you can understand that, right? You draw, better be picasso, y'know the best Cause if this is not so, ah, god bless You leave me no choice, I leave you no voice Believe me son I hate to do it just as bad as you hate to see it done  Now calm your boys,  Cause I'm findin it a little hard to concentrate with all the noise Get the point, I'll let ya go,  Before ya leave, I guess I aughta let you know, I need those keys And promise you never, no matter the weather Evaevaevaevaevaevaevaevaeva come around here no mo'     
  - Coming Of Age
"Coming Of Age"(feat. Memphis Bleek)[] Yeah... Come experience... life as we know it As some of you should know it, yeah, yeah Place, Marcy, Brooklyn Actions... well, y'all know the actions Uhh, I got this shorty on my block always clockin my rocks He likes the style and profile I think he wanna mock He likes the way I walk, he sees my money talkin to honies hawkin I'm the hottest nigga in New York and I see his hunger pains, I know his blood boils He wanna, run with me, I know this kid'll be loyal I watched him make a few ends, to cop his little sneakers and gear then it's just enough for re-up again I see myself in his eyes, I moved from Levi's to Guess to Versace, now it's diamonds like Liberace That's just the natural cycle, nobody wanna be like Michael where I'm from, just them niggaz who banned from a gun We out here trying to make hard white into cohhhhld green I can help shorty blow out like Afro-Sheen Plus I can relive my days of youth which is gone That little nigga's peeps, it's time to put him on[Chorus:  and Memphis Bleek] It's time to come up (and hold my own weight, defend my crown) Gots to lock it down and when they rush (stand my ground) It's time to come up (stick up my chest, and make some loot) Gots to lock it down and when they rush (stand on my own two)[Memphis Bleek] I'm out here slingin bringin the drama, tryin to come up in the game and add a couple of dollar signs to my name I'm out here servin disturbin the peace, life could be better like my man reclined in plush leather seats He's sellin weight, I'm sellin eight... balls sixteen tryin to graduate to pushin quarters y'all I ain't gon' sweat him I'ma let him come to me If he give me the nod then these niggaz gon' see I'm tired of bein out here round the clock and breakin day, and chasin crackers up the block for my pay I'm stayin fresh, so chickens check I'm tryin to step up to the next level, pushin Vettes to the Jets Diamonds reflect from the sun, directly in your equilibirum and stunned I'm waitin for my day to come I got the urge, to splurge, I don't wanna lifetime sentence just give me the word[Chorus][JZ] Hey fella I been watchin you clockin[MB] Who me holdin down this block it ain't nothin You the man nigga now stop frontin[JZ] Hahahh I like your style[MB] Nah, I like YO' style[JZ] Let's drive around awhile[MB] Cool nigga[JZ] Here's a thou'[MB] A G? I ride witchu for free I want the longterm riches and bitches[JZ] Have it all; now listen to me You let them other niggaz get the name, skip the fame Ten thou' or a hundred G keep yo' shit the same[MB] On the low?[JZ] Yeah, the only way to blow You let your shit bubble quietly[MB] AND THEN YOU BLOW![JZ] Hey keep your cool The only way to peep a fool is let him show his hand Then you play your cards[MB] Then he through dealin I understand[JZ] Don't blow your dough on hotties[MB] The only thing I got in this world is my word and my nuts and won't break em for nobody![JZ] Hah, I like resume, pick a day, you can start[MB] From now until death do us part...[Chorus 2X]    
  - Cashmere Thoughts
"Cashmere Thoughts"[ has a conversation with some cat] Hah, hah, hah, hah, yeah, yeah What it is player? You player, it's all about you How you gon' say that man If I had your hand I'd turn mine in Far as I'm concerned, if I had your hand, I cut mines off Hah man, you know man, I'm just dealin that hoe money You know hoe money is slow money but it's sho' money Check this out man, when you run up on your bitch this this is what you tell her Stick they hands in they panties, grab that knot Stick they arm in a car window, drop it like it's hot[] Uhh, I talk jewels and spit diamonds, all cherry like a hymen, when I'm rhymin with remarkable timin Caviar and silk dreams, my voice is linen Spittin venom up in the, minds of young women Mink thoughts to think thoughts type similar Might you remember, my shit is col-l-l-ld like December Smoother than Persian rugs, the cashmere chromosomes make a nigga Jigga  lethal drugs Eighteen carat gold pen, when it hits the sheets Words worth a million like I'm rappin em through platinum teeth I got the Grey Poupon, you been warned Cause all beef return well done filet mignon The Don, smell of Dom on my breath as I yawn, (slow) when you hoes try to con a pro As if you didn't know, Jay's about gettin dough Spittin flow like fine wines down your earlobe I'm smooth but deadly like a pearl handled pistol Honies hum in melody when I, rub it like crystal The proper etiquette, when I drop the subject verb then the predicate, with this rich nigga preterite I'm solid gold, I rap like a mink stole I stick pearl tongues your world'll never know From New York, to Paris, the vocal style vary From nice to deadly like a bad bag of D, now notice, the child swift like a locust Focus on the loc' I be the greatest nigga that wrote it Return of the Jedi, from Rio Degenero Worn da red eye, yet I, still feel the need to be fly I did die when I'm rappin then slide like satin You know the black eye white china in the brain cabinet I never cry if I did I'd cry ice From my nigga Sauce, I hit you with this advice Life's short, so play hard and stick hard and the only time you love em is when your dick hard Whoooh! That's cashmere baby Nah, you know, that's just laid back man Man, shit, J to the A to the Y to the Z Yeah baby Motherfuckin pimp that's what he be Cashmere baby Don't get no hotter than that Sho' you're right Them niggaz know Check it out, check it out Ghettoes, Errol Flynn, hot like heroin Young pimps is sterile when I pimp through your burough in I gotta keep your tricks intact Cause I walk like a p-iyimp, talk like a mack man The star player, the golden bar layer The sweet Ms. Fine Thing puh-layah, sho' yo right I'm game tight, so watch it it change to night Go tell your peeps dawg I'm lethal til it ain't right I pimp hard on a trick, look Fuck if your leg broke bitch, hop up on your good foot     
  - Bring It On
"Bring It On"(feat. Big Jaz, Sauce Money)[Sauce Money] Aiyyo Jay word up; these motherfuckers Fuckin talkin that comeback shit like they cookin crack Shit I ain't frontin all I want my pockets green like slum change Yaknahmsayin? Front the roll we roll back like rubbers motherfucker For real; with no trace of AIDS We keep our pockets fully blown, Roc-A-Fella click nigga Aiyyo we pattin down pussy from Sugarhill to the Shark Bar Fuck a bitch D in the marked car We got the bad bitches gaspin for air in Aspen Searchin for aspirin when I ask then, we swing You cling we do our thing and bring Sling your ding-a-ling from Bed-Stuy Brooklyn to Beijing East coast hostess hostile colossal, money flarin like nostrils for drug dealin apostles, huh Al Pacino down to Nino Brown Me Jay and Primo, got it sewed across the board like poquino Teflon, make sure your jammy is full Cause I heard, Sammy the Bull lamps in Miami with pull Tropical leaves where I got a few keys with my man I'll stock a few G's, now it's unstoppable cheese Said we was garbage, so fuck college Street knowledge amazin to scholars when we coin phrases for dollars Star studded bitches with cristals, get fucked with pistols just to see my shit, discharge puss I drop the stellar, even acapella I got to tell all about Roc-A-Fella[Chorus: Fat Joe] Yeah, bring it on if you think you can hang And if not then let me do my thang[repeat 4X][] Mannerisms of a young Bobby DeNiro, spent spanish wisdoms in a whip with dinero, crime organized like the pharoah I cream, I diamond gleam High post like Akiem, got a lot of things to drop Brooklyn to Queens, I gotta keep my steam Niggaz wanna try to hem my long jeans Uptown fiend for  to appear on the scene In the meanwhile, here's somethin dope for y'all to lean Liason for days on in Money make the world go around so I made songs to spin Can I Live, did dough, with my nigs, dividends flow like the Mississippi riv', lookin jig' Can't do for dolo, had to turn away when Tony killed Manolo That's real, mixed feelings like a mulatto Thug thought he was O.G. Bobby Johnson I played him like Benny Blanco, mano a mano you ain't ready, I find no trigger straight up shoot my guns horizontal, get your weight up, I am two point two pounds you're barely a hundred and twenty-five grams Wouldn't expect y'all to understand this money Do the knowledge, do the few dollars, I'm due to demolish Crews Brooklyn through Hollis to a hood near you, what the fuck... "Bring it on if you think you can hang..." - [Fat Joe][Big Jaz] Money is power I'm into cheddick with facial credit Pure platinum fetish for cheddars Spread letters you move you're deadish I make moves that remove pebbles out of shoes You suck pistol like pipe with the cristal John Stockton couldn't assist you Cowboys or Benzes like we foulin in the U.N. So what the fuck you doin? Whatever nigga Fahrvegnugen, rugged yet polished Spankin dollars with the commas bangin bitches out the Bahamas On hides of llama we cry nada, fly frather Fry hotter, you die gotta Fuck with me witness manana Absence of malice in my palace Call cousin now Dallas trigger finger with the callous Tip scales from mail to keep these niggaz off balance Your frequent stops to O.T.B. you feedin me Steam a nigga schemin on the wrist action with the gleams Jewels for Pop Duke fulfill your dreams Never put the pure brown sugar before the dirty green cream[Chorus] "Yeah, bring it on... bring it on..." - [Fat Joe][repeat 5X]    
  - Regrets
"Regrets"  Stress Sunshine, geyeah I sold it all from crack to o-pium, in third person I don't wanna see em, so I'm rehearsin with my peoples high to GM, from a remote lo-cation in the BM, scopin the whole situation like, "Dayamm!" Metamorphic, as the dope turns to cre-am but one of these buyers got eyes like a Korean It's difficult to read em, the windows to his soul are half closed, I put the key in Pulled off slow, hopin my people flee-in Chink tried to knock the only link that tied me in Coppers was watchin us through nighttime binoculars This time they got us on tape, exchangin dope for dollars Make me wanna, holler back at the crib in the sauna Prayin my people bailed out like Time/Warner Awaitin call, from his kin not the coroner Phone in my hand, nervous confined to a corner Beads of sweat second thoughts on my mind How can I ease the stress and learn to live with these regrets This time... stress... givin this shit up... fuck[Chorus One:] This is the number one rule for your set In order to survive, gotta learn to live with regrets On the, rise to the top, many drop, don't forget In order to survive, gotta learn to live with regrets This is the number one rule for your set In order to survive, gotta learn to live with regrets And through our travels we get seperated, never forget In order to survive, gotta learn to live with regrets As sure as this, Earth is turning souls burning in search of higher learning turning in every direction seeking direction My moms cryin cause her insides are dyin her son tryin her patience, keep her heart racin A million beats a minute, I know I push you to your limit but it's this game love, I'm caught up all in it They make it so you can't prevent it, never give it you gotta take it, can't fake it I keep it authentic My hand got this pistol shakin, cause I sense danger like Camp Crystal Lake and don't wanna shoot him, but I got him, trapped within this infrared dot, bout to hot him and, hit rock bottom No answers to these trick questions, no time shit stressin My life found I got ta live for the right now Time waits for no man, can't turn back the hands once it's too late, gotta learn to live with regrets[Chorus Two:] You used to hold me, told me that I was the best Anything in this world I want I could posess All that made me want is all that I could get In order to survive, gotta learn to live with regrets... (when I was young)[repeat 2X] I found myself reminiscin, remember this one when he was here he was crazy nice with his son I miss him, long as I'm livin he's livin through memories He's there to kill all my suicidal tendencies In heaven lookin over me, or in hell, keepin it cozy I'm comin life on these streets ain't what it's supposed to be Remember Newton, mutual friend well me and him feudin On your life I tried to talk to him But you know niggaz, think they guns can stop foe niggaz Frontin like they're, Big Willie but really old niggaz Hoe niggaz, this year I'm sho' niggaz think I'm slippin I'm bought to send you a roommate, no bullshittin for my hustle's goin too well to hit him You was right niggaz want you to be miserable wit em Anyway, I ain't tryin to hear it, I think I'm touched this whole verse I been talkin to your spirit, a little too much[Chorus One: repeat 2X] Roc-A, Roc-A, Roc-A, Roc-A-Fella y'all     
  - Can I Live
"Can I Live II"[] Geyeah, y'all nigaas finished yo Is y'all niggas finished Got your little radio play your little BDS, huh You finished nigga, huh huh, y'all finished Can I live, huh Can I live, Joe your bein' stingy with the music bin yo[] Yo, yo...yo, I blacks out, I pulls the mack out Scream "Whats that about," then I clap out I get my plot on, in my drop on Through the rotten, dont even hate on those who hate me I got popped on, feelin' it (feelin' it) Chickens are ice grillin' it Cops pullin' it over, Jigga react militant Speed off, officer told me to turn the beat off I turned it a level higher, then return the devils fire I'm raised different, reactin' situations Niggas lay stiff and, rookies blame it on the age difference My subliminal flows create criminal O's Sing along if you with me, til the end of the road I'm cynical when in the view of the public And this is because, I'm defensive when I'm in interviews The percentage who dont understand is higher than the percentage who do Check yourself, what percentage is you? Can I live For all my niggas with all white airforce ones and black guns, stack ones yo Can I live  For all my chicks, pigeons, hoes stand bow legged like the bulldog, know what  I mean, huh? Can I live To all the ce-lo champs, two green dice and one red stop the bank and roll  heads yo Can I live To all my niggas who drink hennesy straight, cop mix tapes, and sell weight  niggas[] I got the feds sending me letters 'cause Im schooling the youth But they cant lock me down 'cause my tool is the truth Yeah I sold drugs for a living, thats a given Why is it? why dont y'all try to visit the neighboorhoods I lived in My mind been through hell, my neighborhood is crime central Where cops lock you more than try to defend you I push you to the limit when I'm needing the wealth And all I see is life cycle just repeatin' itself Ran into shorty boppin' down the ave On his way to clockin' mad then He proceeded to show me a block of slab and said[Memphis Bleek] Aiyyo theres money I there I just gotta have When I catch up to these feinds Im'a knock 'em on they ass Not to brag, sometimes I look at life and laugh How I think about school and it taught me not a ??? When I backed out, let one one, let the barrel turn Holla at you faggots that its my block to burn That credit you dead it, I know heads gettin' annoyed and knew all About a dope feind before reading donald goings Flipping boying, using the right cut One thing thats fucked up is bad dope that I cant pump This slab gotta re-up and rebag, blend it in with the raw Bubble it fast cop more, once I get it I got it I lock it Nobody pop shit, selling twenties on my block bitch For some blacktop shit What you want nigga, what you want nigga What you want, what you want nigga Can I live... To all my niggas that hold coke and they bubble coat Tryin' to win in the construction Timbs yo Can I live... Yo USA, all my chicks that strip, boo's, go to the store with the dewey pins  still in All my chicks with the credit card scams, two kids, one job, and no man All my chicks gettin' that washing set with their welfare check All the mommies dame besa, alright? All my niggas rockin' them fifty cats, tryin' to get at this rap Know what I mean? All my cats with open cases, big cars, and no licenses, I like that shit,  I'll see y'all All my niggas at St. Pauls after they say some fucked up shit Rock on and uh, Jigga shit, Rockafella forever yo Uhh, Major Coins, yeah, uhh huh Memph Bleek nigga     
  - The City Is Mine
"The City Is Mine"(feat. Blackstreet)[] Uh-uhh-uh, ge-ge-geyeah[Chorus: Blackstreet] You belong to the city (Uh-uhh-uh, what what) You belong to the night (Uh-uhh-uh, ge-ge-geyeah) In the river of darkness He's a man of the night[Verse One: ] Uhh, yeah What the deal playboy, just rest your soul I be holding it down yo still love the dough Got these ladies on the cock now you know how we go Got the whole world on lock down you know how we flow Don't worry about Brooklyn I continue to flame Therefore a world with amnesia won't forget your name You held it down long enough, let me take those reigns And just like your spirit the commision remains Niggaz can cross the T's and, dots the I's Now that I got too popular to cop them pies I'm takin this rap shit serious, to my demise Jay shit's like cake mix, watch me rise Basics in the basement, waste it Asking my dog for advice so when he can't say shit my hatred is, fueled just give me a sign And I let the world know that the city is mine, what?[Chorus: Blackstreet] You belong to the city (The city is mine, what-what-what) You belong to the night (Ge-ge-geyeah, uh-uhh-uh, pa-pau) In the river of darkness He's a man of the night (The city is mine, that's right...)[Verse Two:  Y'all want to know how I flow just seek and you find I'm like a brain in the voicebox, I speak my mind About to redefine rap mami, either I'm the illest nigga doing it or these niggaz is losin it I read a article that said I was ruinin shit But every time I look, I'm movin units in quick So I'ma hit y'all, with these last two and split and leave niggaz with nothing but my influences-es Soon it's the Jigga, I ain't mad yeah, bite my shit Sell half of what I sell because it's not quite my shit I'm the type to buy a Roley and just ice my shit on the spot, fuck comin back twice to shit How real is that? My floss game, still intact Boss game, you lame dudes can't feel that Like the first dude to cop the 850 and 89 and drove it up to 55th, the city is mine, what?[Chorus: Blackstreet] You belong to the city (The city is mine) You belong to the night (Yeah, uhh, the city is mine) In the river of darkness (Pa-pa, feel me) He's a man of the night (Yeah, yeah, bounce, bounce)[Verse Three: ] I snatch your girl cause your arm ain't strong enough Plus ya don't stay in the studio long enough I make hits while y'all stay hatin and take bricks Had it locked til I came in the club, Take 6 Got your chick cause you swore she was innocent Got her a Chinese manicure hair done by Dominicans, all for what So I could be in a dark corner, all in the butt at the bar alchoholing her up I represent the lifestyle of those who thirst cream A buck fifty a shot, Louis the Thirteenth , Roc-A-Fella yo, know the name I ain't a player get it right, I'm controllin the game From now until they blow holes in my frame I'ma stand firm, holdin my aim, feel me? I'm the focal, point like Biggie in his prime on the low though - shhhhh, the city is mine![Chorus w/ variations to end]     
  - Intro / A Million And One Questions / Rhyme No More
"Intro / A Million And One Questions / Rhyme No More"[somebody whispering] Somebody's pulling me closer to the ground I ain't panicked, I been here before Seems like only yesterday when I got up on that stage In front of that crowd And showed them who was who, and what was what Man look at these suckers I ain't no rapper, I'm a hustler It just so happens that I know how to rap Okay, I'm reloaded! (music drops in)[] I did it again niggaz Fucked up, right? I know I know what y'all niggaz asking yourself Is he gonna ever fall off? No... ...a lot of speculation on the monies I've made, honeys I've slayed How is he for real? Is that nigga really paid? Hustlers I've met or, dealt with direct Is it true he slay the beef and slept with a tech? What's the position you hold? Can you really match a triple platinum artist buck by buck by only a single goin gold? Roc-A-Fella ship fold, and you're left out in the cold Is it back to charging motherfuckers 11 for an O For the millionth time askin me Questions like Wendy Williams, harrassin me then get upset when I catch feelings Can I get a minute to breathe? And in that minute you leave While I'm looking at my Rol' ice spinnin on my sleeve Uh, nice watch, do you really have a spot? Like you said in Friend or Foe and if so, what block? What you doin in L.A., with phillipinos and ese's Latinos and Cheve's, down by Pico withh Frederico I answer all your questions but then y'all got to go Now the question I ask you is how bad you want to know? BLAOW! Roc-A-Fella y'all, uhh, uh Know my style Motherfuckers can't rhyme no more, bout crime no more Til I'm no more, cause I'm so raw My flow expose holes that they find in yours Wasn't for me, niggaz still be dying for whores But I hate when a nigga sit back, admirin yours Young blood you better get that, we frying baccars Niggaz don't want to be confined to riding the iron horse And don't listen to the rappers, they dying to floss I used to be O.T., applyin the force Shoot up the whole block, then the iron I toss Come back with the click playing Diana Ross I'm the boss and this is how it's gonna be Burnt the turnpike, wild miles on the V I got mouths to feed till they put flowers on me And kiss my cold cheek, chicks crying like I was Cochise Tombstone read 'He Was Holdin No Leaks' Started from the crack game and then so sweet Freaked it to the rap game, Jigga the old-G On MTV, telling em how I sold D And used to back work up out of apartment 4-B Me and my homie, started out coldies Picked the mailbox lock cause I ain't have no key Had the cable with the anchor when Jaz made 'Sophie' Then I went low key, but now I'm back it's on Motherfuckers Jigga, uh-huh, yeah Roc-A-Fella y'all Uhh, feel this     
  - I Know What Girls Like
"I Know What Girls Like"(feat. Lil' Kim, Puff Daddy)[Verse One: ] Peep the scripts Gold honey from the whips Jumped out like YO!  Who the fuck you with Flash the juice 'cause that's the rule Damn I like a girl who spend a little cash for her shoes *** Natural - Can I get at you? Saw a spot on the body look nice with a tattoo With my name, but didn't want to jump the gun I Didn't Know how many niggas was humping hon I said I never seen a face like yours before And I been around some cute whores before That either me or my boys tore it up before So I'm hoping you different  Let you push the 6 And give you a different life and Baby if it's right jump on it in the morning And ride it 'til the night Want to buy you real jury when it hits the light Bitches are momentarily lose they sight She said[Chorus:] I know what boys like I know what they want I know what boys like, boys like I know what boys like I know what they want I know what boys like, boys like me[Verse Two: Lil' Kim] So want a cutie with a booty like OW! Deeper than the MOW! Airy Shine like TADOW! But I'm a real bitch so you know I do real things Only real bitches live like queens - Get it? Safety deposit in the walk-in closet Marvel Forts is for matching Rolls Royce's In the driveway from Monday to Friday I be the richest, shitting on these bitches While chickens cluck giving up the butt I blaze the cut with the daddy raw buff You can call me a slut Who gives a fuck That's fine nigga shit I'm a good with mine I can tell by your shoes you know what I want Fuck a prenup give me half up front My sex be the best so we split these costs You can stop saying mine And start saying ours[Chorus:] I know what girls like I know what they want They want to sex me They think I'm sexy I know what girls like, girls like me I know what boys like I know what they want They want to sex me They think I'm sexy I know what boys like, boys like me[Verse Three: ] Got the bomb place, fireplace John Blaze Victoria Secret lingerie Ice like Don King  The price was like 8 digits a long way, shit Got the beachfront view V1 too Cop you one cop me one too On the place, jetski's park by the lake No neighbors, make all the noise you want to make Invite your friends over Better make their way through  The Benz's and the Rovers before they reach the door Vacate, hey wait, a week or more First class to and fro, freakin off Got the ham things lot Champaigne popped Cruise around the world 'til the damn thing stop Cop rembrandt, handle, pay the lot Can't complain, we balling, true or not?[Chorus: 2x] I know what girls like I know what they want I know what girls like, girls like I know what girls like I know what they want I know what girls like, girls like me I know what boys like I know what they want I know what boys like, boys like I know what boys like I know what they want I know what boys like, boys like me     
  - Imaginary Player
"Imaginary Player"  Yeah I mean like I gotta be like the pioneer to this shit, you know I was popping that Cristal when all y'all niggaz thought it was beer and shit, you know Wearing that platinum shit when all y'all chicks thought it was silver and shit I got to be the pioneer of this shit Bottom line I'm going to show you how to do it Check it[Verse One:] I spit that other shit  That's the nice motherfucker shit Fed time follow me around, deep cover shit nigga You beer money, I'm all year money I'm popping, you ain't got to count it, it's all there money I never change money 'cause niggas got strange money Knocked up, marked up, fucked up in the game money I got bail money, XXL money  You got flash now, one time we'll reveal money I spit the hottest shit, you need it I got it shit That down South Master P, Bout It Bout It shit I got blood money, straight up thug money That brown paper bag under your mattress drug money  You got show dough, little to no dough Sell a bunch of records and you still owe dough  I got 900 and 96 plus 4 more dough You crazy, you full gazy, and loco with dough papo[Chorus: (4x)] Imaginary Players[Verse Two:] And now you got these young cats acting like they slung cats All in they dumb rap, talking about how they funds stack When I see them in the street, I don't see none of that Bad playboy, where the fuck is the hummer at? Where is all the ice with all the platinum under that? Those ain't rolex diamonds, what the fuck you done to that? Y'all rapping-ass niggas, y'all funny to me Selling records, being you but still you want to be me I guess for every buck you make it's like a hundred for me And still you running around thinking you got something on me But I done did it And y'all want to take my flow, and run with it That's cool, I was the first one with it Original, jiggas the future flow digital Still busting a gat when she gets critical Sit it down, I don't want y'all to get it confused I rip it down, like I ain't got nothing to lose[Chorus][Verse Three:] Groupies I leave them all fucked  Niggas - all struck Your single was 99 cents, mines was 4 bucks Last year, when niggas thought it was all up But this year I've done it again, jigga!  What the fuck Nigga stop whining, jigga, still shining Niggas kept complaining so I copped more diamonds Rock more Versace, ain't nothing sweet I still throw t'ree in your body, fleeing the party Y'all can't go with me, nope, flow with me  Bet 50, not dollars either I brought some dough with me I flow like the 5 series, in various areas And blow holes in your weak niggas theories It's funny how one verse can fuck up the game You bought a 4.0 you better get your change Ain't no platinum in those Cartiers, switch your frame Ain't no manicures on board, then switch your plane[Chorus]    
  - The Streets Is Watching
"The Streets Is Watching"  Uh-huh uh huh uh Gee-gee-geyeah Baby, watchin, streets Uh-huh uh huh uh You don't have to look Uh-huh uh The streets is watching Check it, check Uh-huh uh, check Look, if I shoot you, I'm brainless But if you shoot me, then you're famous -- what's a nigga to do? When the, streets is watching, blocks keep clocking Waiting for you to break, make your first mistake Can't ignore it, that's the fastest way to get extorted But my time is money, at twenty-five, I can't afford it Beef is sorted like Godiva, chocolates niggaz you bought it, I pull the slide back and cock it Plan aborted, you and your mans get a pass This rhyme, you're operating on fuck time Y'all niggaz ain't worth my shells, all y'all niggaz tryin to do is hurt my sales, and stop trips to John McNale The type to start a beef then, run to the cops When I see you in the street got, one in the drop Would I rather be on tour getting a, hundred a pop Taking pictures with some bitches, in front of the drop The streets is watching[Chorus] When the, streets is watching Blocks keep clocking Waiting for you to break, make your first mistake Can't ignore it Now it's hard not to kill niggaz It's like a full time job not to kill niggaz, can't chill the streets is watching you, when you froze your arms niggaz wanna test you and your gun goes warm Can't get caught with your feet up, gotta keep your heat up Sweet niggaz running 'round swearing shit is sweeter Once you're tagged lame the game is follow the leader Everybody want a piece of your scrilla, so you gotta keep it realer Kidnap niggaz wanna steal ya Broke niggaz want no cash, they just wanna kill ya for the name, niggaz don't know the rules Disrespectin the game, want you to blow your cool Force your hand, of course that man's plottin Smarten up, the streets is watching, it's on[Chorus] My street mentality flip bricks forever, know me and money we like armed co-defendants, nigga we stick together Shit whatever for this cheddar ran my game into the ground Hustle harder to see if indictment time came around Now you can look up and down the streets and I can't be found Put in twenty-four hour shifts but, that ain't me now Got a face too easy to trace, niggaz mouths got slow leaks Had to hide between my workers, couldn't play those streets She got his face like Mercury you jerkin me? Hectic Had to call upon my wolves to send, niggaz the message I said this: 'Let's play fair and we can stay here I'm trying to transform you Boyz II Men like daycare' Hey there's money to be made and, niggaz got the picture Stopped playing with my paper and, we got richer Then hard times fell upon us, half of my staff had warrants, the other half, in the casket lay dormant I felt like life was cheating me, for the first time in my life I was getting money but it was like my concious was eating me Was this a lesson God teaching me? Was he saying that? I'm playing the game straight from Hell from which few came back like bad coke, pimp or die, was my mindframe bad Was niggaz thinkin simplify was turning cocaine crack? Ain't a whole lot of brain to that, just trying to maintain a stack and knock a lot like two trains that's on the same track 'Fore I get my life together like the oars I bring back In the bottom of the pot where no, water gets hot Got my transporter take it 'cross the border then stop Set up shop with a quarter of rock, here's the plan For three straight weeks, niggaz slaughtered the block But you know the game is 'lluted, fucked up me and my dues One drop can wipe a nigga out, faster than the cops and this unstable way of living just, had to stop Half of my niggaz got time, we done real things By ninety-four became the subject of half of y'all niggaz rhymes Public apoligies to the families of those caught up in my street But that's the life for us lost souls brought up in the streets The life and times of a demonic mind, excited with crime And the lavish luxuries that just excited my mind I figured, 'Shit why risk myself I just write it in rhymes And let you feel me, and if you don't like it then fine' The mindstate, of a nigga who boosted the crime rate so high in one city they send National Guards to get me Ya dig? The streets     
  - Friend Or Foe '98
"Friend Or Foe '98"  I'm done talking Ran up in the spot gun smoking Shot it in the air, one woke him Sun-soaking, sweating in his bed like Dunlo Thinking to himself what done provoked him His thoughts is racing like a vulcan I swear I saw a lightbulb when He finally figured out who was the culprit I said yeah, remember me from Friend or Foe when I told you don't ever ever come around here no more Time to pay now, you try to rise, I wave the gun - lay down This time you're really going to listen to Jay now I try to talk sensibly, hoping that eventually you realize I had this locked and it just wasn't meant to be Plus I had sympathy when we all wore rams with your keys And it wasn't afterthought that maybe you'll try to revenge me But I was like "Nah", Chromes had to know he was wrong And if you caught me on the foul now you would sing me the same song Plus you promised And that's really no fun  Yeah I find you in this Motel 6 with all these guns And all your goons, lined up in adjoining rooms Like some wild cowboys coming to get me at high noon But my mind's like a flower in bloom *** my eyes just scower the room I'm alert, plus I paid the clerk I got it laid out You think you the first nigga I played out, in a 2 hotel town?  Come on now, I peep your Lexus at you Left the exit got some niggas on that side of the town Money well invested, rudely interrupted Jamaican accents ***  A gun in your face and that's all you can come up with? I'm done talking, back up and clap them, one in the abdomen  Do me a favor dude, get 2 ice cubes I pass them Take that ice up, for the nicest MC And please yo, tell BIG, he's unbelievable  Friend or foe BIOTCH!     
  - Lucky Me
"Lucky Me"  How can you fairly assess something from the outside looking in? There's gotta be them times you'll be wrong. Nah Mean? How can a mother fucka go round and hate a nigga  he never even met that he dont even know and shit? I think this rap shit is all beef Y'all dont even know every day I'm livin with stress Got up out the streets you think a nigga could rest Can't even enjoy myself at a party unless I'm on the dance floor hot ass vest You think I'm freakin' these chicks right? I'try not to brush against they chest You get a lawsuit for shit like that, I feel trapped Swear to everything when I leave this earth It's gon' be on both feet, never knees in the dirt You could try me fucka but when I squeeze it hurts, fine We'll lose two lives, yours and mines Gimme any amount of time dont let Ms. Carter grieve at the funeral parlor drippin' tears on my sleeve Told the judge didn't budge it was him or me and I ain't trying to be hard but I'm guilty as charged Put my mercy on this court and my faith in God  And pray hard none of my nephews wanna be stars...Lucky Me[Chorus: Karen Anderson] You only know what you see,  You dont understand what it takes to be me. I hate all girls with alterior motives That's why I'm twenty plus years old, no sons no daughters Hate putting my life in the hands of fake promoters Hear the hate in my voice right? I hate that you noticed Niggas wanna strip to the bone for shit you own Hate a nigga like that faggot, get your own Hate that I can't roam the street without the clip and chrome Knowing one day Im'a have to flip, c'mon You know the shit don't stop 'til the Crist don't pop And you have to kill a nigga and your wrist don't lock I'm trapped the whole worlds against me in fact, It aint no turning back. Bring It On Hate the price of fame cause it cost too much Can I live without y'all niggas saying I floss too much? Hate the way you make this hate flow all through us Steady looking for flaws through us.... Lucky Me[Chorus: Karen Anderson, ] You only know what you see,  You dont understand what it takes to be me You only know what you see,  (Since I was 4 years old, I been told, everything that glitters ain't gold) You dont understand what it takes to be me  (And now that I've arrived I see those truths unfold before my eyes in this world so cold) Nigga see you in the street, pretend to be friendly But I know any type of success breeds envy I know in the back of your mind your conjuring ways to hen me Leave my friends in a circle pouring out Henny But G's is heaven bound so how I'm gon' receive  Anything y'all pour to the ground next time throw it up And ain't nothing changed so even in my afterlife I show it up Dont grieve for me my art remains like a dart from the speaker to your heart Spiritually through the portal now my words as a mortal Plan to leave without a fight I plant a seed I give life Though I can't see past the girls greed to call her wife Next time your thinking heist better be precise Cause I'm fully prepared. One of us is gon' leave here I have no regrets even though I wanna see grow My godsons Boogie, Sonny and Rimo[Chorus x4]    
  - Sunshine
"Sunshine"(feat. Babyface, Foxy Brown)[] What, tssh, y'all, what Jigga, uhh uhh uhh, uh-huh Pa-pa, uhh, pa-pa, uhh The G, Roc-A-Fella y'all Who be, in a Japanese restaurant, eating sushi Drinking saki, it's me, and my mami with the doobie Cutie, smellin like Tiaka, half-Phillipine thing For now, let's call her Suki, got me this booty bangin Properly, in Versace pants, cocky bow-legged stance A thing of beauty, watch me, body crazy Tits Firm like Nature, Foxy, Nas and AZ Truly reason to bug the toolie and keep laced in jewelry watch me Girlie tried to lure me and lock me you gotta get up early Cause who's gettin played is not me "Surely you jest," she said, "if you thought I was purely out for the bucks you woulda bucked stuck and dropped me" I said maturely, "You right but better safe than sorry, but for the lovebirds can move to the suburbs, I need to double check your story To make sure that you one of a kind And you deserve to be my Sunshine"[Chorus: Babyface (variations not listed except for first time)] Touch me with, a heart of gold (uh-huh) I can't go a day without my sunshine (uh-huh) ahh-haaa (say what? uhh) Touch me with, a smile of gold (yeah) I can't go a day without my sunshine, sunshine (uhh, uhh, uhh)[, (Foxy Brown)] A year gone, and she seein things most chicks only hear in songs (uh-huh) keep in gear phenom Lots of ice in the air, round the neck the charm (that's right) Risked a four to life bid to keep that shit on her arm Keep her impressed at all times, cats would love to creep (uh-huh) just to say they crept with mine, slept with mine, she said[Foxy Brown, ()] I ain't deaf nor blind, niggaz stressin Hatin cause they less than mine, they wanna sex me We chose each other, you actin like you chose me They oppose you then, they oppose me We could creep at a low speed, the gat in the hosiery Double cross you they got to triple cross me (I'm thinking that's the way it's supposed to be) Uh-huh (One more thing: If I ever go broke, would you hit the block for me?) Fo' sho' (She replied, eyes open wide) Uhhhh (Put that on everything?) I put that on my life (Right)[Chorus][, (Foxy Brown)] If I needed would you, give me your kidneys? (Uhh, uhh, fo' sho') Catch a case you catch it with me? (Mmm, fo' sho') Pawn your jewlery to come get me? (You better know) Catch me with a chick, forgive me? (Uhh, now that, I don't know) They spread rumors, will you defend me, tooth and nail? (Uh-huh) They try to frame me, will you be there, till the truth prevail? (uhh) (But would you be the same dude, when you blow the roof off sales that you was, throwin rocks, at the Roof at 12, nigga?) This is the truth I shell, till the loot gets frail I put this on my nephews, from the smallest to La'Velle Me and you ballin, from the heavens, or the hell Won't let you hit the ground if I'm fallin myself Now picture me leavin you in this cold world, rollin for delf It's me and you in this old girl, we takin the belt From the lows, to the highs, to the foes we shine Just continue to be my Sunshine (uhhh)[Chorus 2X] 
  - Who You Wit
"Who You Wit II"  Uh-huh, yeah hah Never Sprung huh? Jigga, Roc-a-Fella y'all Never Sprung huh? Yeah, peep the repertoire Peoples, feel me on this one Peoples, feel this Never Sprung huh? Know my style I love bitches, thug bitches, shy bitches Rough bitches, don't matter you my bitches Gold diggers witcha eyes on my riches Can't Knock Your Hustle for real, exotic bitches I'm game tight, see it all through the platinum french frames with the french name in the same night Pull you and your tight friend lift your little dress like light wind, hah, then I slide right in You know the whole repertoire, U.S. to the U-S-S-R Sexin in a Lexus car Match wits with the best of y'all the rest of y'all is like vege-tables in my presence, check it Reminescin to nuttin you ever heard, Iceberg Slim baby ride rims through the suburbs Funds come in lump sums never ends deferred Get money like I'm down South Wednesday the 3rd, it's on[Chorus] Dough to get, more shows to rip I suggest you all roll with the click, who you wit Frozen wrists and it's flows that's sick More O's than you know exist, bitch who you wit Can't scheme on em, Roc-a-Fella got a team on em Chicks dream on him trick cream on him Lose it when dudes think it's just music Lean on em flash green on em and diamond rings on em Sex around the way girls down to mida's I'm somethin every girl gotta have like Levi's Chiquita, me got more, see I brawl You can love me or hate me, either or I'ma stay winnin, rock the custom drop Bentleys Never eat at Denny's and party like Lil Penny can he live? Trick or main chick but if she leave just as quick, indian give, ha-hah Now what I look like? Givin a chick half my trap like she wrote half my raps, yeah, I'm havin that you be the same chick when you leave me the bankbook and the credit cards and take everything you came wit chorus[Chorus] Here's somethin niggaz gon find, not at all funny We takin all ya bitches, takin all ya money  rated A.G. baby that's All Good I sink this ball in your hole, I'm Tiger Woods If the money was the grass and your ass was tee when I hit it with this club love you comin with me Grip you right up under your ass, put your back on the wall Kinda tipsy, seein triple, so I'm fuckin ya all You remind me of this dream I had the night before I'm kinda hopin the condom break to have a reason to go raw I'm playin, hit the showers, hit the money spot Where all the models play and big money is dropped Drop the top, let her feel the moonlight it entranced her She jumped all in my seat like some private dancer I tell you somethin new, if you don't hop down off that butter soft shit with your shoes, I'ma step on the gas She laughed, put her ass back in the proper place She said, 'I played my cards right and look I got the ace' I told her (beatboxes) 'Slow down baby' You dealin with a baller, who, hold ground crazy it's on[Chorus repeat 4X] Beyatch! Fucka Jigga, nine-seven shit, next millenia Recognize, realize, it's on Roc the block y'all Laugh It's on     
  - Face Off
"Face Off"(feat. Sauce Money)[ (Sauce)][ talking:] Sauce mothafuckin, jigga, jigga feel this...[Chorus] This goes out to my Brooklyn crew put ya guns up in the air if ya feel me (If ya feel me) Fuck 'em all day fuck 'em all night we don't love these hoes (This goes out to my Brooklyn crew put ya guns up in the air if ya feel me) If ya feel me (Fuck 'em all day fuck 'em all night we don't love these hoes)[Verse 1] Yeah (If ya want some put ya guns up it's on) Ladies know that when the sun's up I'm gone (Fuck them bitches though digits though) Fuck, now if I bring it niggas know whaat (All black gat with the mack out) I take shorty to the rest blow her back out sun dress undress throw her back out (biotch) (in & out like a crack house) keep it moving (Face off with the .38 scraped off) keep shorty maced can't throw a 4-4 eight ball know your place (so it starts when ya least expect) (the yeast infect) you don't imitate bitches (piece protected) so I hear you hate bitches? (love the dough, ya flow irritate niggas) fuck them though, it's all out and have a fall out I fucked ya girl (On top now we call out fuck the world) (Face Off!)[Chorus] (This gos out to my Brooklyn crew put ya guns up in the air if ya feel me) If ya feel me (Fuck 'em all day fuck 'em all night we don't love these hoes) This goes out to my Brooklyn crew put ya guns up in the air if ya feel me (If ya feel me) Fuck 'em all day fuck 'em all night we don't love these hoes[Verse 2] (I apologize ladies I'm lovin' ya right) you must be used to me trickin' but we fuckin' tonight (No wine no dine) no wheelin' the whip all night long just feelin' the dick be-i-itch (Sauce mothafuckin' slayin' I'm sayin' with no delayin') (Can you beat that? I eat that) you just playin' nigga you neva know what a chick could do (pull the trigga too) check the shit jigga do (My crew) mackin' the same bitch (I do) (back man stack grands) daddy like I you (Love them hoes jigga?) Ha how that sound? women start to fall we all bat around Let my whole team hit it (scatter 'round) you never seen wit it (pat 'em down) check for cream in it (These riches) got nu'hin to do wit these bitches (Nothin' y'all can do to stop these digits) (Face Off!)[Chorus] This goes out to my Brooklyn crew put ya guns up in the air if ya feel me (If ya feel me) Fuck 'em all day fuck 'em all night we don't love these hoes (This goes out to my Brooklyn crew put ya guns up in the air if ya feel me) If ya feel me (Fuck 'em all day fuck 'em all night we don't love these hoes)[Verse 3] (Can I touch that?) what's that? Leave it for dead. Keep ya arm over ya face my nigga (keep ya head) (keep a mind to survive if ya sleep ya dead) Stay fly 'til ya die nigga deep with prayer (with each word ya say I guess the beef is dead) Ladies & gentlemen (like impeach the Prez) (Val Kilmer style nigga draw heat with feds) (broad day like De Niro shoot all day) I'm the man fuckin' the tracks and you just foreplay get a hit I, I come through, blow up, you spit out What keep it cocked faithfully like salop  with one in the drop don't get hit up (I be the 4-5th flamer hoes bitch shamer) (clap cats a snitch she'll give ya whole click name up) Look I done came up (and) thought a whole game up meet me in the square with one in the chamber (The Face Off nigga)[Chorus] This goes out to my Brooklyn crew put ya guns up in the air if ya feel me (If ya feel me) Fuck 'em all day fuck 'em all night we don't love these hoes (This goes out to my Brooklyn crew put ya guns up in the air if ya feel me) If ya feel me (Fuck 'em all day fuck 'em all night we don't love these hoes) This goes out to my Brooklyn crew put ya gun up (in the air) if ya feel me Fuck 'em all day (fuck 'em all night) we don't love these hoes["Track Masters" is whispered softly 8X in background] (This goes out... put ya guns up in the air) if ya feel me if ya feel (Fuck 'em all day fuck 'em all night we don't love these hoes) Yeah!! This goes out (to my Brooklyn crew)...     
  - Real Niggaz
"Real Niggaz"(feat. Too $hort)[] Real niggaz do real things Hangin with the honies is the song I sing Real niggaz do real things On the road to riches and diamond rings Real niggaz do real things Bustin my toast off the roof drinkin 90 proof til spring Real niggaz do real things, check We started out makin, small time bacon Two little niggaz bakin, talkin bout whippin cakes Get clothin and big cheddar, hopin it gets better We had no knowledge of this shit we just was with whatever In front of your buildin clockin, thought I was makin a killin Right in front of your children, eightball in my side pocket They was corrupt too, disrespectin the fiends I used to look up to, take it or leave it, fuck you In different parts of the planet, Oakland to New York I'm hollerin Lifetimes, he hollerin Life's Too $hort Parallel lives and jew-els held high To the Range, to the Rove, get exchanged, for your souls You know how the game goes, slang to get G's and speak in Chinese everybody gains the same dough Get your shit scarred fuckin with my sick squad from Marcy, to the Bay y'all, we get large, keep in charge On the road to riches and diamond rings Real niggaz do real things Hangin with the honies is the song I sing Real niggaz do real things On the road to riches and diamond rings Real niggaz do real things Bustin my toast off the roof drinkin 90 proof til spring Real niggaz do real things[Too $hort] So now you own a record label, I got one too We on a roll now, can't nobody stop our crew You can treat us like convicts, you know we got records On the shelf and on the charts the double deckers The fat donkey house down the block, belongs to me You criticize the way I walk, you wanna see my bankbook? I'm not a crook, I flipped the script and changed my ways so I can get paid, everday I see the same old shit, I see in the streets I know you think I'm sellin keys but I only sell beats Dopefiend music, it's drug related You can buy it on the corner get a radio and play it It always sounds better when you turn it up loud Rap music let these motherfuckers know what we about I know these gay ass record labels keep fuckin niggaz It's just like in the streets main, how much you get?[] On the road to riches, and diamond rings Real niggaz do real things Hangin with the honies is the song I sing Real niggaz do real things On the road to riches and diamond rings Real niggaz do real things Bustin my toast off the roof drinkin 90 proof til spring Real niggaz do real things[Too $hort] That's right, I been a hustler for a long time Always got the right beats, never saying wrong rhymes I started off with nothing ended up with everything Now we sip Hennessee in first class on every plane Ask , he know what I'm sayin Always see me at the bank and yes I'm goin again There ain't no dollar amount, that can make me happy Fine women, a big house, a truck and a Caddy[] Now peep, how sweet, niggaz lives can get Put beef aside, the East and Westside connect $hort Dawg, and Jigga with the, fo'-fo' flow I got love for y'all motherfuckers y'all just don't know I know y'all got a thing for them rag six-fo's I like the five speed drops pop the clutch then go If you want it, keep ballin, and if you jealous stop I want Biggie to rest in peace, as well as 'Pac How real is that? On the road to riches and diamond rings Real niggaz do real things Hangin with the honies is the song I sing Real niggaz do real things On the road to riches and diamond rings Real niggaz do real things Bustin my toast off the roof drinkin 90 proof til spring Real niggaz do real things And I'm out[Too $hort] Beyotch! $hort Dawg's in the house[] Jigga[Too $hort] Much love[] $hort Dawg, get your money main[Too $hort] All the way from the West coast[] Uhh, how real is that     
  - Rap Game / Crack Game
"Rap Game / Crack Game"  Uhh... Uhh, yeah Won't stop niggaz "Somehow the rap game remind me of the crack game" - [Nas] Jigga! Feel me People, told ya motherfuckers, told ya "See that rap shit is really just like sellin smoke" - [OutKast] Uhh, Roc-a-Fella Geyeah We treat this rap shit just like, handlin weight What they want we give it to em, what they abandon we take Hit a rapper with consignment, let him know it's at stake Put his ass in the studio, let him cook up a cake When it's hot, get on my money spot in every state Like the wiz in Camelot, the mom-and-pop's is the gate But first we scope shit, advertise in every area Let the fiends know hey, we got some dope shit Gon' need a middle man, so we look to radio Let em test the product, give em a promo show Just a breeze, not enough to catch a real vibe Then we drop a maxi single and charge em two for five Ain't tryin to, kill em at first just, buildin clientele So when the album drops the first weeks it's on sale But when demand grows it's time to expand yo You don't want no garbage papi it's ten grand per blow, fo' sho' "Somehow the rap game reminds me of the crack game" - [Nas] "See that rap shit is really just like sellin smoke" - [OutKast][repeat 3X] Ge-ge-geyeah I got that uncut raw to make a fiend's body jerk Got your whole block now, pumpin my work My CD's is like keys for you Willie's who like to floss my cassette tapes in sixty-two's And my singles like gems, you know the treys Get you high for a while, but the, high don't stay You need another fix, you better cop these last two bricks Cause when this shit flip, I'ma get on some other shit Never pitchin for a label, Jigga's the hook-up You know my shit is fish scale, y'all niggaz is cook up Just blow up, scream my name from Brooklyn to Da-kota They know my shit stretch without the baking soda Went from an eighth, to a quarter, to a half a key Priority's work wasn't right so I switched factories Now I'm the new nigga, who figured I'd get the game locked Now watch how the prices of your cocaine drop, ha ha "Somehow the rap game reminds me of the crack game" - [Nas] "See that rap shit is really just like sellin smoke" - [OutKast][repeat 4X][cuts and scratches]    
  - Where I'm From
"Where I'm From"  Uh-huh, je-je je-je-jeah ye-ye-yeah, ye-ye-yeah How real is this, how real is this Uh-huh huh, Inspect this here, check[Verse One:] I'm from where the hammer's rung, New's cameras never come You and your man's hung in every verse in your rhyme where the grams is slung, niggas vanish every summer Where the blue vans would come, we throw the work in the can and run Where the plans was to get funds and skate off the set To achieve this goal quicker, sold all my weight wet Faced with immeasurable odds still I get straight bets So I felt some more something and you nothing check I from the other side with other guys don't walk to much And girls in the projects wouldn't fuck us if we talked too much So they ran up Tompkins and sought them dudes to trust I don't know what the fuck they thought, those niggas is foul just like us I'm from where the beef is inevitable, Summertime's unforgetable Boosters in abundance, buy a half-price sweater new Your world was everything, So everything you said you'd do You did it, Couldn't talk about it if you ain't lived it I from where niggas pull your car, and argue all day about Who's the best MC's, Biggie, , and Nas Where the drugs czars evolve, and thugs always are At each other's throats for the love of foreign cars Where cats catch cases, hoping the judge R and R's But most times find themselves locked up behind bars I'm from where they ball and breed rhyme stars I'm from Marcy son, just thought I'd remind y'all[Chorus: 5x] Cough up a lung, where I'm from, Marcy son, Ain't nothing nice Mentally been many places but I'm Brooklyn's own[Verse Two:] I'm from the place where the chruch is the flakiest And niggas is praying to god so long that they Atheist Where you can't put your vest away and say you'll wear it tomorrow Cause the day after we'll be saying, damn I was just with him yesterday I'm a block away from hell, not enough shots away from straight shells An ounce away from a triple beam still using a hand-held weight scale Your laughing, you know the place well Where the Liqour Store's and the base well And Government, fuck Government, niggas polotic themselves Where we call the cops the A-Team cause they hop out of vans and spray things And life expectancy so low we making out wills at eight-teen Where how you get rid of guys who step out of line, your rep solidifies So tell me when I rap you think I give a fuck who criticize? If the shit is lies, god strike me And I got a question, are you forgiving guys who live just like me? We'll never know One day I pray to you and said if I ever blow, Let 'em know Mistakes ain't exactly what takes place in the ghetto Promise fulfilled, but still I feel my job ain't done Cough up a lung, where I'm from, Marcy son, ain't nothing nice[Chorus 4x][Verse Three:] I'm from where they cross-over and clap boards Lost Jehovah in place of rap lords, listen I'm up the block, round the corner, and down the street From where the Pimps, Prostitutes, and the Drug Lords meet We make a million off of beats, cause our stories is deep And fuck tomorrow, as long as the night before was sweet Niggas get lost for weeks in the streets, twisted off weed And no matter the weather, niggas know how to draw heat Whether your four-feet or Minute size, it always starts out with Three dice and shoot the five Niggas thought they douce was live, now hit 'em with trips And I reached down for their money, pa forget about this This time around it's platinum, like the shit on my wrist And this glock on my waist, y'all can't do shit about this Niggas will show you love, That's how they fool thugs Before you know it your lying in a pool of blood[Chorus 4x] 
  - You Must Love Me
"You Must Love Me"[Kelly Price ()] Talking: Throughout my life (uh huh uh huh uh) no matter what I've done.(Right) You've been merciful and your love endureth (yeah) through all things (ye yeah) For that I am eternally grateful.[Verse 1] Since my date of birth bought you nothing but hurt play those video games stole change from ya purse Sat on the cold court bench 'til I was arraigned in ya skirt Saw the pain in ya face through you maintained a smirk All you did was motivate me don't let 'em hold you back What I do I turned around and I sold you crack I was a bastard for that still I'm drowning in shame Just remember one thing now you're not to blame You was newly seperated tryin' to escape ya world and through my thirst I didn't help you I just made things worse I hated me and everybody that created crack Had me thinkin' the newest kicks and the latest gat Still haven't apologized so please play this back while I try to come to terms with such a heinous act you know in more than one way cocaine numbs the brain All I did was think about how the funds once came then I ran across this memory and it stung the brain How can you ever destroy the beauty from which one came That's a savage you're the reason why me and these beats make a marriage why I rhyme above average and I ain't shit Glad you got yourself together no thanks to me Strong and beautiful the way thangs should be You must love me[Chorus (K. Price) (You must love me repeats in background)] Say that you love me All I know say that you must love me. Ohh yeah[Verse 2] We used to fight every night but I never would suffer just smile my big brother's tryna make me tougher As we grew fussing and fighting continued as I plundered through ya stuff and snuck ya clothes to school Got intense real intense as we got older Never believed it would lead to be popped in one in ya shoulda Where my rings? Knew you had it 'cause you took too long as Mickey, Andy, and the girl that bought it looked on Huffin' and puffin' gun in my hand told you step outside Hoping you said no but you hurt my pride made our way down the steps maybe you thought it was just a threat or maybe ya life was just that crazy and you was beggin' for death try to justify this in my young mind but ya drillin' it and my ego hurt combined drove me berzerk Saw the devil in your eyes high off more than weed confused I just closed my young eyes and squeezed What a sound opened my eyes just in time to see ya stumbling to the ground Damn what the fuck I done now runnin' around in a circle thinking I'm assed out hot gun burnin' my waist ran straight to Jazz' house Like a stranger damn I just shot my nigga and ran off into the night as if it was not my nigga Left the scene how could I go out that way Still you asked to see me in the hospital ya next day You must love me.[Chorus (You must love me repeats in background)] What after all the wrong I've done I know you must[Verse 3 (Starts over last line of chorus)] Everything in my power and within my frame to protect you from this life and keep you away from the game But you was one of the few people that I can trust and the fact of the matter I slang these pies for us You put the pressure on me dearly rarely would you let it go Was a thousand and one times I had to tell you no When it was one of those days when nobody was around and I needed emergency trip out of town Searched my mental rolodex for all the numbers I know As you stared in my face asking me could you go I'm agreed said sender everything'll go smooth just tell her what to do and everything'll go through Strapped her body with them thangs as you boarded the plane Couldn't explain these strange feelings that I caught and the pain I'm thinkin' why would I send you when I knew it ain't right I'm thinkin' what would make you sacrifice ya life You must love me[Chorus (You must love me repeats in background)] After everything that I've done wrong I know inside you must love me I know that you love me You showed me I know it I know Say that you love me say that you love me I know you must love me Oh yes you do Inside I know it you've always shown it you love me yea yeah Oh yeah I know that you love me  
  - Intro - Hand It Down
"Intro - Hand It Down"(feat. Memphis Bleek)  Sorry boys.. but all the money in the world couldn't bring me back again Lay down, lay down Gonna stretch my mic out in Ponce Funeral Home on Marcy All those new niggaz stop there but a lot later than a whole gang of people thought The last of the real hustlers, well maybe not the last Bleek's gonna be a good rapper New, IMPROVED  I quit I'm retirin Ain't enough money in THIS game, to keep me around Sorry Big, I tried Honest Can't go with me on this ride though I'm callin the shots The bar's closing Where we going to for breakfast? Roc-a-Fella y'all OKAY, I'M RELOADED! "Bringin the drama"  "Tryin to come up in the game" "Marcy" "Had a couple of dollar signs to my name" "Roc-a-Fella y'all" "One of the best!" "Waitin for my day to come" "Just give me the word"[Memphis Bleek] Nah this ain't Jigga it's your lil nigga Bleek Reportin to these motherfuckers live from the street Game I peeped those, my mind so advanced At nine I used to geese hoes for Easter clothes Peep the steez, I represent for all those with 28 grams, on a come-up tryin to creep the keys Large niggaz told me park the car, keep the keys Find a hoodrat and creep to Mickey D's First gun two bullets, niggaz know I do pull it Niggaz tryin to kill me dog, who wouldn't? Screw Gooden, I pitch in the PJ's Lit off the EJ, I split Dutchies with my ring finger You find a bitch that don't be cream, bring her Last seen with Bing, he got dropped between us Shit is constant, that's why I pack the Johnson and Johnson for the nonsense who wants it? I go to sleep with a picture of a Porsche on my wall Man I'm tryin to come up on y'all Get one up on y'all, that's why I hustle in these streets from sundown to sunup on y'all Mama said keep bullshittin they'll kill you dead One week of this hustlin brought a living room set Went to ? D's, niggaz mad, veins out Copped the Jordan's, two weeks before they came out Flashy, fly little nigga Nosy bitch from the third floor like "Why little nigga?" Bitch please, twist the trees Took a long pull, like bitch to breathe That's my answer, life's like cancer And I'm serious "Waitin for my day to come" "Just give me the word"     
  - Hard Knock Life (Ghetto Anthem)
"Hard Knock Life (Ghetto Anthem)"[] Check the bassline out, uh-huh Jigga (bounce wit it), uh-huh uh-huh uh-huh, yeahh Let it bump though["Annie" sample] It's the hard knock life (uh-huh) for us It's the hard knock life, for us!! Steada treated, we get tricked Steada kisses, we get kicked It's the hard knock life!![] From standin on the corners boppin to drivin some of the hottest cars New York has ever seen For droppin some of the hottest verses rap has ever heard From the dope spot, with the smoke Glock fleein the murder scene, you know me well from nightmares of a lonely cell, my only hell But since when y'all niggaz know me to fail? Fuck naw Where all my niggaz with the rubber grips, bust shots And if you with me mom I rub on your tits, and what-not I'm from the school of the hard knocks, we must not let outsiders violate our blocks, and my plot let's stick up the world and split it fifty/fifty, uh-huh Let's take the dough and stay real jiggy, uh-huh And sip the Cris' and get pissy-pissy Flow infinitely like the memory of my nigga Biggie, baby! You know it's hell when I come through The life and times of Shawn Carter  nigga Volume 2, y'all niggaz get ready["Annie" sample] It's the hard knock life, for us  It's the hard knock life, for us!! Steada treated, we get tricked Steada kisses, we get kicked It's the hard knock life!![] I flow for those 'dro'ed out; all my niggaz  locked down in the ten by fo', controllin the house We live in hard knocks, we don't take over we borrow blocks Burn em down and you can have it back daddy, I'd rather that I flow for chicks wishin, they ain't have to strip to pay tuition I see you vision mama, I put my money on the longshots All my ballers that's born to clock Now I'ma be on top whether I perform or not I went from lukewarm to hot; sleepin on futons and cots to King Size, dream machines, the green fives I've seen pies let the thing between my eyes analyze life's ills Then I put it down type braile I'm tight grill with the phony, rappers y'all might feel we homies I'm like still, y'all don't know me, shit! I'm tight grill when my situation ain't improvin I'm tryin to murder everything movin, feel me?!["Annie" sample] It's the hard knock life, for us  It's the hard knock life, for us!! Steada treated, we get tricked Steada kisses, we get kicked It's the hard knock life, for us  It's the hard knock life, for us!! Steada treated, we get tricked Steada kisses, we get kicked It's the hard knock life!! [] I don't how to sleep, I gotta eat, stay on my toes Gotta a lot of beef, so logically, I prey on my foes Hustling's still inside of me, and as far as progress you'd be hard-pressed, to find another rapper hot as me I gave you prophecy on my first joint, and y'all lamed out Didn't really appreciate it, til the second one came out So I stretched the game out, X'ed your name out Put Jigga on top, and drop albums non-stop for ya, nigguh!["Annie" sample] It's the hard knock life, for us  It's the hard knock life, for us!! Steada treated, we get tricked Steada kisses, we get kicked It's the hard knock life, for us  It's the hard knock life, for us!! Steada treated, we get tricked Steada kisses, we get kicked It's the hard knock life!! .. It's the hard knock life!! .. It's the hard knock life!!     
  - If I Should Die
"If I Should Die"(feat. Da Ranjahz (Half Dead & Mais))[] Come on...life...death...here...gone...Yo If I should die don't cry my niggas just ride my niggas bust bullets in the sky my niggas And when I'm gone don't mourn my niggas get on my niggas when it's real say word to Shawn my niggas If I should die [echoes] Don't cry my niggas it's been one hell of a ride my niggas in the middle of the trial I flip pies my niggas I did joints with Mary J. Blige my niggas I've eluded the coppers got booted with Big Poppa Skated through with the Ceasar Picadas At high school got head by the lockers gassed the baddest girl in the class to show me her knockers rocked jewels dropped school still didn't fail rhymes still written well hold court in the street never sit in the cell for a second then I'm gettin' my bail shoot it out with the bounty hunters fuck sittin' in the county for summers if they should down me everybody around us become one for that day to live life get your shit right & play Don't get it twisted like rays if I miss that's ok but life's short don't miss a day uhh If I should die don't cry my niggas just ride my niggas bust bullets in the sky my niggas and when I'm gone don't mourn my niggas get on my niggas when it's real say word to Shawn my niggas If I should die...[Wais] ...don't cry my niggas it's been one hell of a ride my niggas say word to Wais my niggas when I'm gone don't mourn my niggas just keep gettin' it on my niggas say word is bond my niggas I got a lot to look back on in '88 got my crack on ten years later gettin' my rap on gettin' shorties like a thespian had an episode with two lesbians got a fetish for that drunk ginseng with Japanese chicks & pulled the root out squeeze my whole clip to survive shootouts been on both coasts fired all kinds of heat probably be kinda glad to leave these mean streets I got dead mens to meet and questions to fulfill like is that mystery God real? and how was Kennedy killed? I ain't mad I must've smoked a ton of reefer sipped Coronas with Latifah broke the code of Geneva I know when I reach the other side I'ma see the cat I had beef with who blood remains on my sneaker then it's on again if I could be born again I live my life through my son and tell him never have a friend just family reincarnated I'll show him the time that I waited to get paid tell him never be afraid niggas hearts pump Kool Aid and yo blood run thicker never shed tears cry liquor my nigga If I die don't cry my niggas it's been one hell of a ride my niggas say word to Wais my niggas when I'm gone don't mourn my niggas just keep bangin' these songs my niggas say word is bond my niggas If I die...[Half Dead] ...don't cry my niggas just stay gettin' high my niggas don't wonder why my niggas when I'm gone live on my niggas just follow my path my niggas say word to Half my nigga I'm the aftermath of pleasure never die alone born to live forever through life's struggles I cut corners & took drastic measures see you niggas life expire right in front of me time could never mend what these cold streets mentally done to me too often I close my eyes and see my own coffin feelin' haunted ready to leave this world that I'm lost in my only chance to see the seeds I lost through abortion when I'm gone y'all niggas better not mourn keep flossin' as long as my name lives on what's most important I'll be down in hell scorchin' preparin' for life afterlife still torchin' & blazin' these mics It'd rain for 40 days & 40 nights & I'd return on the 3rd like Christ without my physical portion my spirit a poltergeist for sure I'll be back through the heist tomorrow blood over y'all fake niggas door What you thought? (huh)  What you thought? (nigga) If I should die don't cry my niggas just stay gettin' high my niggas don't wonder why my niggas when I'm gone live on my niggas just follow my path my niggas say word to Half my nigga When I die...     
  - Ride Or Die
"Ride Or Die"  I'm rollin with Roc-a-Fella man Cause they got money man, heh heh Uh-huh, uh-huh uh UH, uh-huh, 'Hovah Yeah, Stevie J nigga Y'all ready? Yo, yo How many y'all wanna ride tonight (ride tonight) How many y'all down to die tonight (die tonight) How many y'all wanna ride tonight Nigga ride or die or ride or die[repeat 3X] Aiyyo fuck y'all, niggaz I crush y'all, rush y'all with the four drawn and I touch y'all, plus y'all little motherfuckers ain't ready for war I seen your team in a Chrysler before, but I forgot? The same rules apply, don't try to switch up your style Y'all niggaz is pumpkin pie, and that's plain as I much better than you cat, shocked when I got the news that this nigga ready for war, well where that fool at? I bruise wack rap niggaz severely punish them Especially those that get fucked for they publishing, heh Always gotta be the weakest nigga out the crew I probably make more money off yo' album, than you You see the respect I get everytime I come through Check your own videos, you'll always be number two Niggaz talkin real greasy on them R&B records but I'm platinum a million times nigga, check the credits S. Carter, ghost writer, and for the right price I can even make YO' shit tighter I roast niggaz like ya, smoke niggaz like ya Take your little jewels and put the toast to niggaz like ya You know what the fuck we do and why we done it How I bring it to niggaz who, probably want it Keep playin, you gon' find me in your lobby blunted And I don't even smoke nigga, ain't no joke Niggaz cat fightin with Jigga, kickin sneaky shit Makin little tapes but keepin it secret Cause I kick that deep shit that divide your peeps shit Now I don't know if you fuckin with Jigga spittin that weak shit y'all How many y'all wanna ride tonight (ride tonight) How many y'all down to die tonight (die tonight) How many y'all wanna ride tonight Nigga ride or die or ride or die[repeat 2X] Yeah, yeah Niggaz don't want it with Jig, cause somethin got to give I got homes where you hide, I hustle where you live Jigga's the Don, bitches scream "Jigga dandy, dick is the bomb, about as thick as a arm" Mr. Exxon, gas 'em with the wit and the charm Bitch I'm tryin to tell you like Nichalous Bond I'm a big cat, listen mami, can you dig that? Cars, jewelry, homes, I did that Oh's, shootouts, keys, I live that Actresses, models, chickenheads, hit that I get stacks and still I kick back and run up on niggaz with the midac, where the shit at? How many y'all wanna ride tonight (ride tonight) How many y'all down to die tonight (die tonight) How many y'all wanna ride tonight Nigga ride or die or ride or die[repeat 2X] Time to seperate the platinum from the white gold, right from the door The real from the fake, ready rock from the raw The boss from the runners, cats who ride dick from the cats with the numbers, the five from the six I got cop n crash money, pop the dash money Press the button, alluva sudden, glock in the stash money Beef with Jigga, watch yo' ass Money It's El Presidente, top brass money Now I don't flash the steel, I blast for real My motto: you only good as the last nigga you kill I'm here to snatch this meal, nigga that's for real If you rollin with me grab the wheel, let's ride huh? How many y'all wanna ride tonight (ride tonight) How many y'all down to die tonight (die tonight) How many y'all wanna ride tonight Nigga ride or die or ride or die[repeat 4X]    
  - Nigga What, Nigga Who (Originator '99)
"Nigga What, Nigga Who (Originator '99)"(feat. Big Jaz)[] Uh-huh uh-huh, gi-gi gi-geyeah Roc-a-Fella y'all, uh-huh uh-huh, Jigga Timbaland shit, nine-eight BEYOTCH Say what, say what? Uh-huh uh-huh, follow me beotch Nigga what, nigga who? Nigga what, nigga who? Switcha flow, getcha dough Can't fuck with this Roc-a-Fella shit doe Switcha flow, getcha dough Can't fuck with this Roc-a-Fella shit doe[ (first four lines overlap the section above)] Can't fuck with me They ain't ready yet Uh-huh uh-huh Yeah, yeah Motherfuckers wanna act loco, hit em wit, numerous shots with the fo'-fo' Faggots wanna talk to Po-Po's, smoke em like cocoa Fuck rap, coke by the boatload Fuck dat, on the run-by, gun high, one eye closed Left holes through some guy clothes Stop your bullshittin, glock with the full clip Motherfuckers better duck when the fool spit One shot could make a nigga do a full flip See the nigga layin shocked when the bullet hit Oh hey ma, how you, know niggaz wanna buy you But see me I wanna _Fuck for Free_ like Akinyele Now I gotta let her take this ride, make you feel it inside your belly, if it's tight get the K-Y Jelly All night get you wide up inside the telly Side to side, til you say  you're too much for me[Chorus:  (with Amil-lion)] (Nigga what?) Make you think you can fuck with me (Nigga who?) Recognize girl, Jay to the Z[repeat 3X] (Nigga what?) Make you think you can fuck with me (Nigga who?) Recognize bitch, Jay to the motherfuckin Z[] Got a condo with nuttin but condoms in it The same place where the rhymes is invented So all I do is rap and sex, imagine how I stroke See how I was flowin on my last cassette? Rapid-fire like I'm blastin a Tec, never jam though Never get high, never run out of ammo Niggaz hatin n shit cause I slayed your bitch You know your favorite, I know it made you sick And now you're, actin raw but you never had war Don't know how to carry your hoe, wanna marry your hoe Now she's mad at me, causer Your Majesty, just happened to be A pimp with a tragedy She wanted, us to end, cause I fucked with friends She gave me one more chance and I fucked her again I seen her tears as she busted in, I said, "Shit.. there's a draft, shut the door bitch and come on in!"[Chorus (with variation in last line)][] Gotta vendetta even though I been better Left him in the cold with a thin sweater Rap niggaz on Prozac get the bozack, niggaz threw two at me I threw fo' back, hold that Let the dough stack, way before Big had the gold Ac' Dame had the Lex black Motherfuckers wanna test that, stress that And right where you're stressed, where you rest at I suggest that, niggaz invest, in a vest, when I come through with the glock jet black, you niggaz step back I'm the best at, you know I ain't no apprentice to this Me and my niggaz we invented the shit I came into the business with this, The Originator, non greater Jaz-O finish this shit[Big Jaz] Better learn, Jaz'll relax that, ever heard of me? Worldwide Originator, say word to me The population holla certainly, I burn a nigga like a third degree, see me shine so bright Nigga I'm my light, runnin rulin with rigor and vigor Nobody bigger than me and my nigga Jigga You fly-by-nights stop chirpin B Heavyweights type work to me For the time, in this motherfucker ain't nobody hurtin me What? Cut your face in like surgery Who the fuck got a VS, fuckin BM's on the road when you had to be in bed at the PM Need the info, Jaz on the C-N-N forever touchin my workers beginnin you're endin Nigga your style's no style my style's hostile C'mon, faggot nigga down to take the gun home O-R-I-G-I-N-A-T-O-R (can't FUCK with it can ya?!)[Chorus (with variations)][Amil-lion (repeat to fade)] Switcha flow, getcha dough Can't fuck with this Roc-a-Fella shit doe Switcha flow, getcha dough Can't fuck with this Roc-a-Fella shit doe     
  - Money, Cash, Hoes
"Money, Cash, Hoes"[:] Turn the lights all the way Turn the lights all the way down What Uhhuh Yeah  (Uhh) Come on Big flow (GGRRRRRR) Come on yeah come on  Yo Yo J-A-Y, I flow sick Fuck all y'all haters blow dick I spits the game for those that throw bricks Money cash hoes money cash chicks what Sex murder and mayhem romance for the street Only wife of mines is a life of crime And since, life's a bitch in mini-skirts and big chests How can I not flirt with death  That's life's a nigga, long as life prevent us We gonna send a lot and pray to Christ forgive us Fuck it Ice the wrists and raise the price on these niggaz Y'all cant floss on my level I'll invite you all to get wit us if ya ball is glitter When I go all the harlem playaz wall my picture If you get close enough you can read the scripture It reads money cash hoes how real was that nigga what[Chorus: repeat 2X] Money cash hoes money cash hoes (WHAT) Money cash hoes money cash hoes (UHH) Money cash hoes money cash hoes (COME ON) Money cash hoes (WHAT) hoes (WHAT) hoes (WHAT) Flavors robust platinum and gold touch  Y'all rap now, fast money lets slow it up Niggaz try to stop  to no luck Roc-A-Fella foreva CEO what what Us the villains, fuck your feelings While yall playa hate we in the upper millions Whats the dealings (huh) its like New York's been soft Ever since Snoop came through and crushed the buildings I'm tryin to restore the feelings fuck the law keep dealing More money more cash more chilling I know they gone criticize the hook on this song Like I give a fuck I'm just a crook on this song Bed-Stuy Brooknon took on the world  Shit I led a life you can write a book on Sex murder and mayhem romance for the street  Man and I tell ya itll be the best seller[Chorus: 2X][DMX:] D-M-X and my dogs bite Jigga my nigga rhyme all night Thugs for life one night with this rap shit Let em go and I bet they know what'll happen  When we clap shit Actin like we owe em something Then we show em something Talk greasy I think they found em down the road or something Fuckin wit a madman in a bad mood Its like fuckin wit a mad dog that wasnt fed food And the only thing thats stoppin him is you  Cause the only thing that he'll be droppin is you Topic include; choppin in two Drop it to Clue and the response from the street This was one dog that loves raw meat But gettin back to just cause I, love my niggaz  I shed blood, for my niggaz  Let a nigga holler where my niggaz All I'ma hear is right here my nigga [Chorus: 2X] Roc-A-Fella shit uhhuh Ruff Ryders My nigga Swizz Uhhuh uhhuh Dont stop biatch Uh Uhhuh yeah  Inspect the game yo     
  - A Week Ago
"A Week Ago"(feat. Too $hort)[] Uh-huh[$hort] That's right[] Uh-huh-uh, it was all good just a week ago[$hort] Last week I had everything[] Uh, uh-huh-uh, had this all good just a week ago[$hort] I had the money.. had the cars, the bitches[] Uh-huh, yeah, it was all good just a week ago[$hort] and the jewelry.. and then my motherfuckin niggaz started snitchin[] Uh-huh, uh uh, yo[$hort] Beyotch![Verse One: ] Growin up in the hood just my dog and me We used to hustle in the hood for, all to see Problems, I called on him, he called on me We wasn't quite partners, I hit him off my P Met him unlocked doors, off my keys Yeah we spoke, much more than cordially Man he broke bread with me, my business spreads with me The Feds came to get me, we both fled quickly Wasn't quick enough to jump over the hedges with me Got caught, and that's when our relationship strayed Used to call me from the joint til he ran out of change And when he called collect and I heard his name I quickly accepted, but when I reached the phone he's talkin reckless, I can sense deceit in his tone I said, "Damn dawg, what, nine weeks and you're home?" He said, "Main man, you think shit's sweet cause you're home." I just sat, spat no more speech in the phone The crackers up there bleachin your dome, you're reachin I said, "The world don't stop I've got to keep keep on." From there I sensed the beef was on I ran to the spot, store to add some more features to my phone To see if I had bugs and leeches on my phone Can't be too safe cause niggaz is two-faced And they show the other side when they catch a new case It's on[Chorus: Too $hort, ] It was cool when you had hella weed to smoke And you bought a new home where you could keep the folks I don't see how this side of you could be provoked (Uh-huh, uh-huh, it was all good just a week ago) Funny what, seven days can change A stand up nigga, now you sit down to aim Used to have a firm grip now you droppin names Uh-huh, uh-huh (It was all good just a week ago)[Verse Two: ] Like I put the toast to your head and made you sell We both came in this game, blind as hell I did a little better, had more clientele Told you put away some cheddar now you cryin for bail Seventeen and I'm holdin on to around a mill I could bail out and blow trial and come around on the pill Had niggaz thinkin I was from Uptown for real I had so much hustle plus I was down to ill Like a Brooklyn nigga, straight out of Brownsville Down and dirty, down to fight the round thirty Freezin on them corners still holdin my crack Lookin up and down the block, the fuck is the dough at? Came from flat broke to lettin the dough stack You tell them feds I said I'm never goin back I'm from Marcy, and Marcy don't raise no rats You know the consequences of your acts, you can't be serious[Chorus][Verse Three: ] The lawyer I retained you said you leakin some things All this after a week in the bang I'm mad at myself cause I didn't spot the weak and lame I woulda bet the house you wouldn't speak a thang Nigga this was the oath, to the top of broke Even pricked our finger, anything that got between us we sposed to cock the ninas, what happened to that? Instead you copped out to a misdemeanor Fuck it, the same thing make you laugh make you cry That's right, the same game that make you mad could make you die It's a dice game, and sometimes you crap Who woulda thought you'd get popped one time and rap? Now you know that's bad when your sister is mad and your son gotta grow up like, "This is my dad?" The labelling of a snitch is a lifetime scar You'll always be in jail nigga, just minus the bars[Chorus][Too $hort] Shit is crazy man All these niggaz out here snitchin We was one step away from takin this crack money and recyclin it through the ghettoes and buildin back up our own hoods Now all you niggaz start snitchin on each other I got partners doin 15-20 Wouldn'ta been doin SHIT if you didn't snitch Beyotch! It's about time y'all check that shit out man It ain't all good Shut your mouth Just watch the game And don't snitch It sure will do a lot for you Believe that baby , Short Dawg's in the house main You know I got it Got it goin on We got the money Ain't got nuthin to do with crime baby But I'm recognizing[] You rat bastard!     
  - Coming Of Age (Da Sequel)
"Coming Of Age (Da Sequel)"(feat. Memphis Bleek)[] Uh-huh uh yeah, gi-gi-geyeah Time to come up, hold my own weight, defend my crown Gots to lock it down and when they rush -- part two[Bleek] Cocaine whiter now[] Operation is sweet[Bleek] Whole game tighter now[] Movin a brick a week[Bleek] Plus a nigga price is down[] We them niggaz to see[Bleek] Time to start the arisin now[] I don't know what's wrong with Bleek[] It seems, I'm like Keenan, pickin up on the vibe that he ain't too happy, I could just see it in his eyes I don't know if it's the chicks or how we dividin the loot Time to pay his ass a visit 'fore he decide to get cute Jumped out like a star with the flavest car Matchin the gator shirt, softer than my next door neighbors These young niggaz think I fell out the loop cause the last time they seen me hoppin, out the Coupe I hopped out in a suit[Memphis Bleek] Look at this nigga Jay frontin tryin to take my shine I didn't say this verbally, just had some shit on my mind Plus I'm puffin like an ounce, more than I used to puff Takin advice from these niggaz but they ain't used to stuff They had me thinkin, "Shit, I'm the one that moved the stuff while he drive around town in brand new Coupe's and stufF" Swear to God, they had me practically hatin his guts As he approached I spoke, "Jigga whattup?"[Chorus: Memphis Bleek] I done came up (uhh) put my life on the line (uhh) Soaked the game up (yeah) now it's my time to shine Time to change up (what?) no more second in line Nine-eight, these streets is mine  (uh-huh, uh-huh, uh-huh-uh-huh-uh-huh)[] Look at that fake smile he just gave me, it's breakin my heart Should I school him or pull the tools out and just break him apart I felt his hatred it was harsh, 'fore this fakin shit start I should take him in back of the building and blaze him[Memphis Bleek] Uh-oh, this nigga Jay he ain't slow, he musta picked up on the vibe and had I, not been so high I woulda been able to hide Tried to cover up myself, as I gave him a five Hugged him, as if I loved him[] To the naked eye It woulda seemed we was the closest, but to those that know us could see that somethin was about to go down[Memphis Bleek] Stay focused I'm tryin to concentrate, but it's like he's reading my mind As if he can see through this fog and all this weed in my mind Could he see I had plans on, bein the man Ever since we first spoke and he put that G in my hand And I gave it back to show him, I was down for the cause As he approached ("Whattup Bleek?") and I paused..[Chorus: Memphis Bleek, ] I done came up (uhh) put my life on the line (uhh) Soaked the game up (yeah) now it's my time to shine Time to change up (what?) no more second in line Nine-eight, these streets is mine  Yeah, you done came up (uhh) put your life on the line (uhh) Soaked the game up (yeah) now it's yo' time to shine Time to change up, no more second in line[Bleek] Nine-eight, these streets is mine[] Right, yo we wild out in Vegas, styled on haters Mouthed off at the cops, I done crammed every drop Copped whips the same color, we tighter than brothers with different fathers but same mothers, this life don't love us So til death do us, I'm never breakin my bond Nigga we Lex movers, V-12 pushers[Memphis Bleek] As I stand One leg of my pants up, in a stance like, "Man what?" I know these niggaz are peepin my mind cancer But in time's the answer Seems mind-blowin, this weed and Hennesey Got my mind goin, trust me nigga, I'm knowin Chicks used to ignore me, and my aunt sayin I need fifty not sixty-forty[] Oh God, don't let him control y'all Your gun is my gun, your clip is my clip baby[Memphis Bleek] Your fun is my fun (uh-huh) your bitch is my bitch Any nigga tryin to harm Jay I'm feelin for you I ain't only touchin you, I'm killin your crew[] Give it a year, you'll be sittin on a million or two records sold nigga, perfect your roll, geyeah[Chorus: Memphis Bleek] I done came up (came up) put my life on the line Soaked the game up (game up) now it's my time to shine Time to change up (change up) no more second in line Nine-eight, these streets is mine (what, geyeah geyeah) I done came up (came up) put my life on the line Soaked the game up (game up) now it's my time to shine Time to change up (change up) no more second in line Nine-eight, these streets is mine[] Yeah, you done came up (uhh) put your life on the line (uhh) Soaked the game up (yeah) now it's yo' time to shine Time to change up, no more second in line Yeah, yeah Coming of Age Two, brand new     
  - Can I Get A...
"Can I Get A..."[] What? Well fuck you... bitch Bounce wit me, wit me, wit me wit me Can you bounce wit me, bounce wit me, wit me wit me Can you bounce wit me, bounce wit me, ge-gi-gi-gi-gi-gi Can you bounce wit me, bounce wit me, ye-ye-yeah Uh-huh uh-huh bounce wit me, bounce wit me Can ya can ya can ya bounce wit me, bounce wit me Ya-yah-yah, ya-ya-yah-yeah bounce wit me, bounce wit me Ge-gi, ge-gi-gi-gi-geyeah bounce wit me, bounce wit me Get it![Verse One: ] Can I hit in the MORNIN without givin you half of my dough And even worse if I was broke would you WANT ME? If I couldn't get you finer things like all of them diamond rings bitches KILL FOR would you STILL ROLL? If we couldn't see the sun risin off the shore of Thailand would you RIDE THEN, if I wasn't DRIVIN? If I wasn't ah, eight figure nigga by the name of Jigga would you come around me or would you clown me? If I couldn't flow futuristic would ya put your two lips on my wood and kiss it - could ya see yourself with a nigga workin harder than 9 to 5 contend with six, two jobs to survive, or do you need a BALLA? So you can shop and tear the MALL UP? Brag, tell your friends what I BOUGHT YA If you couldn't see yourself with a nigga when his dough is low Baby girl, if this is so, yo..[Chorus: x2][] Can I get a FUCK YOU to these bitches from all of my niggaz who don't love hoes, they get no dough[Amil] Can I get a WOOP WOOP to these niggaz from all of my bitches who don't got love for niggaz without dubs?[Amil] Now can you bounce wit me, uhh[] Bounce wit me, bounce wit me Can ya can ya can ya bounce wit me, bounce wit me[Amil] Uh uh.. Major Coins, Amil-lion[] Bounce wit me, bounce wit me[Amil] Uhh, yo bounce wit me[] Can ya can ya can ya bounce wit me, bounce wit me[Amil] Yeah, uh-uh uh uh[Verse Two: Amil] You ain't gotta be rich but FUCK THAT How we gonna get around your BUS PASS Fo' I put this pussy on your mustache Can you AFFORD ME, my niggaz breadwinners, never corny Ambition makes me, so horny Not the fussin and the frontin If you got nuttin, baby boy, you betta "Git Up, Git Out and get somethin" Shit! I like a, lot of P-rada, Alize and Vodka Late nights, candlelight, then I tear the cock up Get it up I put it down erytime it pop up, huh I got to snap em, let it loose, then I knock ya Feel the juice, then I got ya, when you produce a rocka I let you meet momma and introduce you to poppa My, coochie remains in a Gucci name Never test my patience nigga, I'm high maintenance HIGH CLASS, if you ain't rollin, bypass If you ain't holdin, I dash yo[Chorus][] Now can you bounce for me, bounce for me[Ja] Uhh[] Can ya can ya can ya bounce wit me, bounce wit me[Ja] Uhh![] Gi-gi-gi-geyeah-geyeah[] Can ya bounce wit me, bounce wit me[Ja] UHH![] Gi-gi-gi-gi can ya bounce wit me, bounce wit me[Ja] Uhh! Yeah[Verse Three: Ja (Rule)] It ain't even a question how my dough flows, I'm good to these bad hoes Like my bush wet and undry like damp clothes What y'all niggaz don't know, it's eazy, to pimp a hoe Bitches betta have my, money fo' sho' Before they go, runnin they mouth, promotin half I be dickin they, back out, go 'head, let it out I fucks with my gat out, bounce and leave a hundred Makin em feel, slutted even if they don't want it It's been SO LONG since I met a chick ain't on my tips but then I'm DEAD WRONG, when I tell em BE GONE So HOLD ON to the feelin of flossin and platinum cause from NOW ON, you can witness Ja the I-CON with hoodies and TIMBS ON, cause I thugs my bitches VeVe, studs my bitches, then we rob bitch niggaz I'm talkin bout straight figures if you here, you wit us If not Boo, you know what, I still fucked you[Chorus][] Now can you bounce wit me, bounce wit me Ge-gi, ge-gi-gi-gi bounce wit me, bounce wit me Wit me wit me wit me bounce wit me, bounce wit me Bounce, bitch, bounce.. wit me wit me wit me wit me Can ya bounce wit me wit me Ge-gi, uh-huh uh-huh uh-huh uh-huh Uh-huh uh-huh uh-huh uh-huh uh-huh uh-huh uh Can ya bounce wit me bounce wit me Geyeah     
  - Paper Chase
"Paper Chase"(feat. Foxy Brown)[Foxy Brown] Uhh, uhh, uh-huh Uhh (paper chase) Bonnie n Clyde Y'all motherfuckers know how it's goin down (gotta get that paper y'all) That's right, uhh (Uh-huh uh, yeah, Roc-a-Fella, yeah Paper chase y'all, paper chase WHAT? Uh) Greyhound bitch, stay down bitch Bout to set up shop with Jay, round this bitch Half a brick of yea, bout to lay down this bitch (til November?) Nah, I'm here to like slay down this bitch What you think? I don't wanna have to spray down this bitch Call my whole team, from around the way down this bitch I'm tryin to stay down this bitch, play down this bitch Had a sound, so my nigga Jay drown the six Roll the windows down and, weight round this bitch But there's a couple things 'fore it's OK round this bitch Gotta talk to the natives, let em know I'm here  for all to get the paydays, first I line up all the haters I got jobs for ya, drop stars for ya More arms than Green Bay's Brett Favre for ya Money providentials hope that's not a problem for ya If so, Jigga be here, day after tomorrow for ya (That's right!)[Chorus: Foxy, ][F] Gotta get that paper dog[F] Gotta touch that, love that, paper dog, uhh![J] Gotta get that paper dog[J] Gotta have that grab that paper dog![F] Gotta get that paper dog[F] Gotta spend that, bend that, split that, get that[J] Gotta get that paper dog[J] When I needs that, G stack, tell me where the weed's at?[] I got my two guns, I came to scoop ones A down ass bitch and she down to click Got a nice little hooptie that I get around with And my plan is, not to leave this town til I'm rich Gotta find a nigga sellin all them ounces and shit Tell them get down with the click or get found in a ditch See I drop down and strip, I turn around and spit Not to hit em, just to let em know the sound of shit Return later that evening in the club with Fox And I got the snub nosed for those that love to box I'm in search of them young niggaz that hug the block all day, til it's like gray outside Shoot dice talkin shit all day outside And even when it's hot, they outside Let em know, how it's gon' go, Bonnie n Clyde And aiyyo, you will want me on your side[Chorus][] Yo, yeah, I got that stress and I got it the best I ain't got it to give but I got it to test And if you wanna get down, all you gotta invest is your time, I gotta move this in a, week or less For the next couple of days I brought her all I posess The Rolex, necklaces with the VVS Twin to drive in the passenger with a TV rest For my top draft picks I cop the new GS Now all the little soldiers wanna roll with my team Cause I ain't sold em a dream, I just showed em the cream Picked em up in the afternoons and told em some things You know the regular shit you do when you moldin them teens Yo, never lay your head where you holdin them things From family, to your business, nothing goes in between Never feared no man, put four in his Beem Drop your gun then, blow the scene, ya heard me?[Chorus]    
  - Reservoir Dogs
"Reservoir Dogs"(feat. Beanie Sigel, The LOX, Sauce Money)[Sheek] Fuck -- shit is real right here Roc-a-Fella, LOX, takin the streets over motherfuckers Don't get it twisted Yo, aiyyo, aiyyo, aiyyo Yo shut the fuck up 'fore I blast and Banned From TV your ass with no mask, look at the camera like what? Yeah I did it like them sick white boys the court committed To the death of me, I'm spaz like I'm on Ecstasy Drop 100 bars for real like I'm lookin for a deal If I ain't hungry, who the fuck is, I'm worse than them African kids I ain't straight til my numbers match the Motorola ?bid? And walk the streets up in ? ? like I don't fuckin care If I ain't strapped that means I took em off my Nike Airs Get off mine, y'all talk shit like little children when I ride mine like bitched when I walk up in the building Cause I catch tans in the winter, with wild whores Jet-skiin, while you keep warm at corner stores I make it hot, floodin your block, the best way Professionally, they'll find poison in your X-Ray As I get roasted lookin at Biggie posted on my wall Takin shots of Louie til I fall Nuttin to lose, just load the clip up in the groove and kick rhymes to the poster, til I swear Big move My team, you would think was on Thorazine How we floss and don't give a fuck what it's cost-ing[Beanie Sigel] Yo, yo, pressure bust pipes, it's time to apply it now Pick out a quiet town and tie it down Make niggaz lock it down, y'all know where to buy it now Beanie Mac I supply it now My squad roll deep, in foreign cars with two seats Couple of 5's, a 6, a few Jeeps Bag enough coke to last a few weeks In case niggaz wanna test, vest and a few heats You really wanna test my name? And test my game? Until you have me, test my aim? Y'all niggaz nuts, like testricles Hit you up in your apartment buildin vestibule Perhaps it's best for you, to keep on walkin Heat from the noggin, keep on sparkin Platinum prezzie, Bezzie, stay sparklin Cop off the lot never see me at the auction Pint of Bacardi darken, when it's hawkin Out on the strip, until I reach the margin Not tryin to meet the Seargeant, at the precinct Eatin cheese sandwiches, down for the weekend Locked up with dirty white boys and Ricans[Jadakiss] Now if I kill you I probably do ten in the box Come down on appeal then I'm killin your pops You feelin The LOX, nigga why you grillin The LOX If this rap shit don't work niggaz still in the spot You bring it to me, I gotta lose your family Gangstas don't die, they get chubby, and move to Miami Shit is deep now dog but it gets deeper Fuck it, the weather's nice and the price is much cheaper I put it on tape, you gon' buy it, I put it in a bag you gon' try it, y'all niggaz can't deny it Lot of cats still tryin to study my last bounce Tell you what, get a beat tape and a half ounce They got me where I can't be without my large gat Teflon long sleeve, and my hardhat Don't matter if I'm openin up, or headline Doin the speed limit or pushin red lines Six months in the county or fed time I'ma be the 'Kiss nigga, until it's bedtime Anything I'm on is a classic, any nigga ever had beef with, son is a bastard Anytime I spit, spit acid, L.O.X. Ruffryder you heard? We got the game mastered I told you the pain was comin You wouldn't listen You tried to play me like a joke? Now who got the last laugh? Now take these bullets with you to hell[Sauce Money] You motherfuckers is sick, don't think Sauce the shit So many niggaz on my nuts I thought I lost my dick Picture me fallin off, I'm camera shy Hammers fly, might miss you, but your man'll die What's the difference? Either way I'm stunnin your crew I fuck to win, y'all niggaz comin to lose Somethin to prove? Spit it, we can have a sprayoff I lay off wet niggaz and kill em on my day off Ain't nuttin for me to bust a trey off Murder the whole month of April nigga, just to take May off Run with more Germans than Adolf, you light crews Now I concentrate on your camp, like Jews Flow hot like a heatwave bitch Whips fatter than them shits they beat slaves with I'm a meal stackin nigga who pull quick, still packin for you Phil Jackson niggaz on that Bull[Styles] I don't give a FUCK who you are, so FUCK who you are I don't care about a pretty bitch, watch or a car I don't care about your block and whoever you shot I don't care about your album and whenever it drop I don't care about your past if I did I woulda asked I'm too busy lightin 'dro with a whole lotta hash Far as this rap shit, I'm ten steps ahead of niggaz Shootin backwards, just for practice Ride or die nigga, hoppin in your casket Bout to go to hell with you, blow the L with you Tell the whole world I'm spittin let em know the shells hit you I tell niggaz quick, suck dick and get a glock My name ring bells like Sunday at twelve o'clock I'm half past seven, bust six then eleven You know me, slide my man my joint say reload me I ruffryde and pop a fella for Roc-a-Fella Jay (what the fuck) spendin mozzarella[] I know pop you can't stand us cause you cock them hammers Run in your crib, no prisoners, pop your grandma Locked in the slammer? Nope, popped up in Atlanta Crossed up in a drop I popped up the antenna Whoa.. watch your manners when my veins pop like scanners Like raindrops you hear the thunder when I cock the cannon Big thang, big chains, ain't shit changed Get brained in the four dot six Range Shit main, switch lanes every town I hit, switch planes, bitch flipped big caine Flow with no cut, you take it in vain/vein to the brain Muh'fukas is noddin and throwin up, you know that You don't wanna owe that man He'll hit you, get the picture? Kodak man Gotta, love for war, I don't floss no more I just sit on my money til I'm above the law How the fuck you gonna stop us with your measly asses We don't stop at the tolls we got EZ passes, nigga Multiple cars and divas with D-classes Iceberg sweat with I.B. on the elastic Shit, beyotch! What the fuck, ya heard me? Put some more beat on that joint     
  - It's Like That
"It's Like That"(feat. Kid Capri)[] Yeah, un huh, watch this y'all, come on,watch this y'all, Jigga Roc-a-fella ya'll, uhhhh, come on yea ![Kid Capri] It's Kid Capri and , It's Kid Capri and  Cause I'm Like That yo ! Cause I'm like that yo ![Verse One: ] As a young and dumb man, gun in the waist Sold crack to those who couldn't take the pain And had to numb it with baste Couldn't drink the henny straight, I needed somethin to chase I needed something to chase Nowadays I throw shots back,leavin nothin to waste Life is like a treadmill, niggas runnin in place Gettin nowhere fast, a whole year done past > I vowed to never stop winnin, 'til the earth stop spinnin Rock hot lenin, cop hot cars and hot women If it's not him then you got it confused, y'all not remembering, My motto is simply I will not lose, abide by the block rules, I buy my glock used, wit bodies on it, let me know anybody want it ? I'm raised, illrational, way misunderstood, If you ain't live like I live then run with the hood I done what i could, to come up with this paper 'til this day still Run with the hood, guess it's part of my nature, if hell awaits ya ? Nigga I'm coming with the razors, still flashin ya shit Try to pass me in a six, tight classy on the wrist Every bit of 30 karats, this is not a game This isn't why I came, make these words find a spot on your brain And burn, then I recycle my life I shall return[Chorus: Female voice and Jay- Z][Woman] How tight is your flow ?[] Cause I'm like that yo ![Woman] How right is your dough ?[] Cause I'm like that yo ![Woman] How white is your blow ?[] Cause I'm like that yo ![Woman] Only writers you know[] Cause I'm like that[Verse 2: ] I'm a hop, skip, a jump, from rippin the pump Spittin a couple of curse words, and hittin you chump Shit, I get digits in lumps, I'm a motherfucking problem is this what you want ? Overachiever, I love chicks that puff chiva, And reefer paper, I hate the one's that blow up ya beeper Cause I, go in ya deeper, I only bone divas Inpregnate the world when I "cum" through your speakers (ha ha) Fuck hot my records got the fever Niggas kick dirt, get ya whole block sweeped up I creep up when the beef heats up, caught him with his feet up And shoes off, bout to snooze off Hatin, cause you can't turn the booze off You dudes is too soft, when I fuck with you all I might bark your ex, and spit at the locks But, other than that I ain't even fucking with cats Just me tied B.I., thug it like that, me,dame and biggs What's fuckin with that ? Y'all can never diss Jigga, get nothing for that Other then a couple slugs in ya back,[huh huh] Rappers y'all runnin around, like I won't gun ya down Last nigga that fronted, two spun him around Lord, except this offer here's somethin for your crown I admit no malice, I just met his challenge, In one[Chorus: Repeat 3x][: Repeat 2x til fade] Girls and guns, all i want stock exchange, rocks and thangs  
  - It's Alright
"It's Alright"(feat. Memphis Bleek)[:] Bounce if you wanna bounce, ball if you wanna ball Play if you wanna play, floss if you wanna floss It's Alright, you heard?, It's Alright, Holla back Get ill if you wanna ill, smoke if you wanna smoke Kill if you wanna kill, loc if you wanna loc It's Alright, you heard? It's Alright, yeah yeah I need a ho in my life to blow on my dice So we can make our points twice and skate out a town I need that glow in my ice, E-Class Ladies screamin Jigga you know we ease that, flowin out like Jees-ass  and me holdin the mic so when you like you find MC's so impolite And me I'm so into nice, got cats on the corner like Don't me and Jigga be flowin alike?  Nah, Not in your life ain't nobody copin like Mr. , shit you're crazy I'm hot like the six maybe, Deep dish with the great seats I flow greater than you're navigator I drop in you're town, block you're data Pimps all comin through with a hot pair of gators And a crew with rocks the size of craters Can't touch like hot potatoes, Ya Heard? Bounce if you wanna bounce, ball if you wanna ball Play if you wanna play, floss if you wanna floss It's Alright, you heard?, It's Alright, Holla back Get ill if you wanna ill, smoke if you wanna smoke Kill if you wanna kill, loc if you wanna loc It's Alright, you heard? It's Alright, Holla back[Memphis Bleek:] In the middle of a war rockin a vest Who's the illest shorty alive, I confess I take nine to the chest and I swear to the heaven sky's, I bless The mics until the day I rest, till they can feel what I feel I'ma try my best, and if you real like I real you can provide the rest Anything left out, you can blame it on the brain, not the heart I'm playing my part, stretched out, just about the best out Any nigga realer than me, is in a messhall with their chest out Any rapper with less clout, sell more records than me We extort them as soon as they record 'em, Bleek My name is clear, back when a shorty used to braid my hair On the project stairs, Once I drop to a ceaser Ma I don't need ya From the block to the hot two-seaters [:] Bounce if you wanna bounce, ball if you wanna ball Play if you wanna play, floss if you wanna floss It's Alright, you heard?, It's Alright, Holla back Get ill if you wanna ill, smoke if you wanna smoke Kill if you wanna kill, loc if you wanna loc It's Alright, you heard? It's Alright, Check On the two Jew-el's I blew more money than Latrell, who else? They don't know you, think they know you too well, you jell Like Flubber I hover above the city in a private jet, the livest set Press you're brakes, Feds wanna investigate, Mr. I don't cop nothin Less than eight, and anything involved with my name Regardless of the fame It's hard, I can't even walk through Harlem again, Charge it to the game, I'm platinum like American Express My boy died, and all I did was inherit his stress To make every jam tougher, you ain't my man fuck ya I suggest let you live right? Negative, I swear It's dough or die, I hope your soul provides you with an afterlife Close you're casket tight Take you're last two deep breaths and pass the mic  To  nigga, That's Right!! Bounce if you wanna bounce, ball if you wanna ball Play if you wanna play, floss if you wanna floss It's Alright, you heard?, It's Alright, Holla back Get ill if you wanna ill, smoke if you wanna smoke Kill if you wanna kill, loc if you wanna loc It's Alright, you heard? It's Alright     
  - Money Ain't A Thang
"Money Ain't A Thang"(feat. Jermaine Dupri)  Uh uh So So Def Yeah, yeah[Chorus: Jermaine Dupri and ][Jermaine Dupri] In the Ferrari or Jaguar, switchin four lanes With the top down screamin out Money ain't a thang[] Bubble hard in the double R flashin the rings With the window cracked, holler back Money ain't a thang[Jermaine Dupri] Jigga, I don't like it if it don't gleam clean And to hell with the price cause the money ain't a thang[] Put it down hard for my dogs that's locked in the bang When you hit the bricks, new whips Money ain't a thang[Jermaine Dupri] Come on, y'all wanna floss wit us Cause all across the ball we burn it up Drop a little paper, baby toss it up Ya slackin on your pimpin, turn it up See the money ain't a thang[] I flex the rol', sign a check for yo' hoe Jigga's style is love, X and O Save all your accolades, just the dough My game is wide, all lames aside Tryin to stay alive, hundred thou' for the bracelet Foolish, ain't I? The chain'll strain ya eye Twin platinum gun son, aim for the sky Ice on my bullet, you die soon as I pull it Willies wanna rub shoulders, your money's too young See me when it gets older, ya bank account grow up Mine's is one-zero-zero-zero-zero-oh-doub' Damn near out the rear trunk when I roll up Multi til I close up, it's all basic I been spending hundreds since they had small faces Rob your stash house, doubled out down in Vegas Me and Jermaine Dupri got it locked crazy Where you at haters?[Repeat 1][Jermaine Dupri] My cake thick, I live the life Eatin' crab, watching bitches shake shit all night I make the big moves, do the big things Take small groups, turn them into big names The big dog with the big chain, frost bit bracelet to match Cats say I'm the shit man The type of nigga that you need in yo' crew Type of dude that will do shit you won't do, can't do Get more burnt than a candle Too hot to hold, too much to handle In the black C-low, he know if she look She go bye-bye with da-da and I ain't gotta say no more I'm the truth like A.I., got the proof and stay fly In the safest shit you could never buy Know why? Cause I write the songs that the whole world sing I don't know bout y'all but every night I swing[Repeat 1][] Ya'll shit ain't for real til y'all ship a mil' And ya hit a R&B chick and she fit the bill Said she loved my necklace, started relaxin Now that's what the fuck I call a chain reaction Went from wholesome to Jigga, you owed some Baby, I don't play all my jewelry is light grey Platinum, spend your whole life in the day What's down is a bet, roll the dice[Jermaine Dupri] Yeah, yeah, so let's play  So what, you went gold and rock a Roley with the ice bezel It's gonna take a lot more to see my level Where I'm at, your check, you better double that And personally your raps is where the trouble at I'm a Benz bubble cat, leather with the wood grain In the platinum frame screaming it's not a game Gleaming, from ear to ear, wrist to wrist, ring and chain Even me and  got it locked, crazy[Repeat Chorus] So So Def, Roc-A-Fella, collabo' You know, all we do is rock Rock on  
  - Hova Song (Intro)
"Hova Song (Intro)"(feat. Pain In Da Ass)[] Yeah, I know you just ripped the packaging off your CD If you like me you readin the credits right now If you in your car, I don't care if it's winter I want you to put all your windows down Zone out, buckle up, let's go Hello it's Hova; that's right young'un the wait is over The new millineum is upon us, the album is here Before we get into the shit, let's get a few things clear Rappers with no relation: there's "Seven Degrees of Seperation" and I'm Kevin Bacon This is the murderer's version Jigga the shit, even when he rhyme in third person Hova the God, I should be rappin with turban Haters can't disturb him, waiters can't serve him Mike Jordan of rap - outside J workin Now watch how quickly I drop 50 I don't like playin, niggaz can't stick me Niggaz can not jam me, niggaz can't get me Slimmy at the Rucka wanna leave and spend with me I consistantly take em out the park like Ken Griffey Do you believe? It's Hova the God[Pain In Da Ass] Makes you think about the people in your life Then I think about BIG; what'd he say if he was here He'd say, "Jay, what's it about? What's life about? If you don't go through as a man's a man" He'd say, "Suck it up, take the fall, do the time  that's what makes you who you are, makes you what you are" How many years you been around this thing of ours? Commision, 125 years What's it about? It's about rules, parameters You take the beatin for the friend you don't lay down you don't betray who you are, what you are You gotta remember guys like Taj, Chill, Ran, Emory They don't roar, they don't rap You know why? That's the rules, you don't break them You was born to be somethin I wasn't even supposed to be.. humble Okaay so you humble me now, what you got? You got a war, you got global war  You got a worldwide crime syndicate now There's no rules, there's no parameters, there's no feelings There's no feelings for this game So.. five ten years from now You're gonna wish there was American Commision Five ten years from now... They're gonna miss  Oahhhkayyyyy, I'm reloaded!!!!!     
  - So Ghetto
"So Ghetto"[] Back at'cha How we do Primo, Jigga-Man History in the making Let's go Uhh, uh-huh-uh-UHH Uh-huh-uh-uhh, uhh I spit the murder-murder-murderous Mur-mur-ma-murderous SHIT Uh-huh-uh-huh-uh-huh-uh-UHH I keep the gangsta-gangsta-gangsta Gah-gah-ga-gangsta beat, feel me? Uhh I spit that Brooklyn-Brooklyn-Brook Uh-uhh, uh-huh-uh-uhh, uh-uhh Uh-huh-UHH Yo.. career crook, nobody rap Brooklyn like me Jigga-Man, Volume 3, I'm back lookin like me Stop the presses, baby girls, drop your dresses B-K lick a shot for Big Pop' in heaven Ever since I came through, niggaz got the impression everything I drop, out of the question, stop the guessin it's hot, flows provin I pack cause my dough's movin My whole crew up in this muh'fucker We spray corners, stand there like you got a cape on ya, fine You'll be wearing a black suit a long time I put your crew in hard bottoms The priest is like, "God's got him He never did nuttin to nobody but them boys shot him" Brandish iron, outlandish buyin Bentley Coupes, not braggin just simply the truth We all from the ghetto, only difference, we go back Back up in D&D on this Primo track, listen[Chorus:  {scratching by DJ Premier}] I'm so gangsta prissy chicks don't wanna fuck with me "Iceberg, Slim baby ride rims" I'm so gutter, ghetto girls fall in love with me "You know him well.." "..by the name of Jigga" I'm so gangsta prissy chicks don't wanna fuck with me "You can love me or hate me.." ".." I'm so gutter, ghetto girls fall in love with me "Roc-a-Fella lock the whole block down"[] Wednesday's I'm up in Shine, Cheetah's Monday night I'm fuckin with the model chicks Friday night at Life So I'm cruisin in the car with this boozy broad She said, "Jigga-Man you rich, take the doo-rag off" Hit a U-turn; ma I'm droppin you back off Front of the club, "Jigga why you do that for?" Thug nigga til the end, tell a friend bitch Won't change for no paper plus I been rich Eighty-eight been hustlin, linen been crushin em Women been fuckin them HUH? You see I live for the love of the street Rap to the ruggedest beats Hall closet cluttered with heat I spit that murder-murder-murder that Brook-Brook-a-Brooklyn shit Furthermore ma.. We tote guns to the Grammy's, pop bottles on the White House lawn Guess I'm just the same old Shawn[Chorus][] I'm from the M-to-the-A-baby-R-C-Y So it's hard for me to let the larceny die Niggaz see me in the streets with no bodyguards just two big guns that'll body your squad Could niggaz be scheamin on me? Probably are Think Jigga's a joke nigga? Hardy har I spit Brook-Brook-Brooklyn every time I bust Radio's gotta play me though I cuss too much Magazine said I'm shallow, I never learned to swim Still they put me on they cover cause I earn for them Soon as I sell too much, watch them turn on him cause that seem to be the shit that'll earn for them I spit that murder-murder-murderous everytime a verbalist iller than Verbal Kint is or O-Dog in "Menace" I'm ill, start to finish, I rip apart contenders I'm hot.. hehehehe..[Chorus][] I'm so gangsta prissy chicks don't wanna fuck with me, uhh I'm so gutter, ghetto girls .. Heheh, (uhh, uhh, uh-huh-uh-uhh), yeah Uhh, yeah, funk, yeah, with me, yeah, beyotch, yeah Jigga, yeah, Primo, yeah, gangsta, yeah, niggaz, yeah Brooklyn, yeah     
  - Do It Again
"Do It Again"(feat. Amil, Beanie Sigel)[] Roc-A-Fella Y'all know what this is We givin y'all five seconds to put your drinks down and report to the dance floor immediately All the bustas we giving y'all five seconds to get close to an exit It's about to get real ugly in here Five Seconds is up Let's go! Throw the hands up (uh, uh, uh) Throw the hands up (Niggaz) Throw the hands up (Bitches) Throw the hands up (Bustas) Throw the hands up (Hustlers) Throw the hands up (Hos) Throw the hands up (Posta's) Throw the hands up (MAC)[Beanie Sigel] You know how Mac come through on the club tip Everybody real deep on that thug shit Cop Cris' spray the club on that thug shit Cop frisks suits snub in the club quick Told y'all real high, when I come through You can try if you want to, you can die if you want to We hittin whores on the floor, whole crew be wild Bitch "Back That Azz Up" like Juvenile (huh) When my peeps come through to spend a dime apiece You know Mac come through with a line of freaks Every bitch on the hit be a 9 at least We getting head on the floor, while you grinding freaks Whole squad get it down like this Whole squad buying rounds of Cris Whole squad got they crowns on wrist Whole squad got a pound of twist Whole squad got a pound to spit In case a clown wanna flip Mac never slip in a club, told y'all niggas 4/5th in a club If a nigga wanna draw then the blood it can drip in the club You know how niggaz get in the club, shit you know how I be All high in VIP, rolling up to B.I.G. (Baby) Niggaz be all liquored up talkin shit Till' they man gotta come pick them up Got bitches in the back bouncin to "Jigga What" You got your hands up and I ain't even stick y'all up Throw the hands up (uh, uh, uh, Everybody get it up) Throw the hands up[ (Amil)] 12 AM on the way to the club (uh) 1 AM DJ made it erupt (uh-huh) 2 AM now I'm gettin with her (what up?) 3 AM now I'm splittin with her (splitting with who?) 4 AM at the waffle house (waffle house) 5 AM now we at my house (uh) 6 AM I be diggin her out (who?) 6:15 I be kickin her out (what?) 7 AM I'ma call my friends (uh-huh) 12AM we gonna do it again, we gon, we gon, we gonna do it again (We gonna do it again)[] By the way yo Yo, how the fuck you gonna talk about MC's on our hill When we just cop them things homey the chromy wheels Both arms are chunky the sleeves on chill Any given times 100 G's in your grill Don't talk to me bout MC's got skillz He's alright but he's not real 's that deal with seeds in a field Never fear for war, hug, squeeze that steel Fuck, you gotta a flow that's cool with me You gotta lil' dough that cool with me You gotta little cars little jewelries But none of y'all motherfuckers could fool with me You know the wrist frost bit minus two degrees Bout as blue as the sea the way I manuever the V Hat cocked can't see his eyes, who could it be? With that new blue Yankee on, who but me? Niggaz shift two million, then I blew the three Then I skated the four, before I went on tour I came back and it's plain Y'all niggaz ain't rappin the same Fuck the flow y'all jackin our slang I seen the same shit happen to Kane Three cuts in your eyebrow tryin to wild out The game is ours will never foul out Y'all just better hope we gracefully bow out Throw your hands up Niggaz, Bitches, Bustas, Hustlers FUCK THAT (Throw the hands up)[Amil ()] 12 AM on the way to the club (uh huh) 1 AM bout to shake the butt (uh) 2 AM now I'm checkin the mix (ah yeah) 3 AM now he buyin me drinks (what you drinkin on) 4 AM exit the club (let's go) 5 AM think he gettin some butt (that's right) 6 AM nigga still ain't bust (what) 6:15 nigga will get up (uh) 7 AM gotta tell my friends (ah huh) 12 AM I'ma do it again, uh, uh I'ma Do it again 12 AM we gonna do it again (Uh, uh Let's go)[] 12 AM on the way to the club 1 AM DJ made it a rub 2 AM now I'm gettin with her 3 AM now I'm splittin with her 4 AM at the waffle house 5 AM now we at my house 6 AM I be diggin her out 6:15 I be kickin her out 7 AM I'ma call my friends 12 AM We gonna do it again, we gon, we gon, we gonna do it again Let's go     
  - Dope Man
"Dope Man"(feat. Serena Altschul)[sound of a camera taking a picture][Jay] Millenium flow[MTV] Serena Altschul's here live outside the criminal courthouse[Jay] This is {bullshit} y'all[MTV] in New York City for the first day in the trial of [Jay] I'm gone [car speeds off][MTV] the State vs. Shawn Carter, a.k.a. [Jay] Uhh, uh-huh-uh, uhh, uh-huh-uh, uhh[MTV] Whatever the verdict in this trial may be the effects will undoubtedly be felt worldwide[] Aiyyo, stand forward, 'fore you take notice or witness to me killin the track Testify 'til me spillin the smack Now they got me for traffickin, racketeerin, audio crack[Hook:] They call me Dope Man, Dope Man I try to tell em I'm where hope, floats man Ghetto spokes-man A broke man, approachin the bench with intent to bury me under the cell, fingered me as the toast man Evidence stemmin from ninety-six They say the world ain't recovered from his fix While they was usin cut I was on some other shit Gave it to you raw and they just discovered it Nowaday, the jury got they brow raised Listenin to testimony about my foul ways Exhibit A: "Reasonable Doubt" They say this was the first thing that turned the peoples out[MTV] You can feel the tension building here as an unprecedented number of people have turned out for what may be the "Trial of the Century"[Hook][] How come, you label your brand of dope "Volume 1" and spread it through the slums? Fed it to the young with total disregard Your honor, the State seeks the maximum charge And how could you, turn right around and release a lethal dosage called "Volume 2" And is true you operate the criminal enterprise known as Roc-a-Fella in charge of his meteoric rise? And do you deny you're responsible for the demise of record execs, and do you object? Your distribution's Polygram, and through your connects Def Jam, you pushed over five million SoundScan And not to mention, your co-horts and henchmen Dame, Biggs, Lyor, Kev' and Russell Simmons And we ain't gon' talk about Murder, Inc. That just establishes a darker deeper criminal link[MTV] The State is seeking the maximum penalty and with the overwhelming amount of evidence the D.A.'s presented, things aren't looking good[Hook][MTV] Despite the grim outlook at this point the rapper has been known to emerge triumphant in the face of adversity[Hook][MTV]  is taking the stand[] Right hand on the Bible, left hand in the air Before I spoke one word, made sure my throat was clear A-hem, I'm a prisoner of circumstance Frail nigga, I couldn't much work with my hands But my mind was strong, I grew where you hold your blacks up Trap us, expect us not to pick gats up Where you drop your cracks off by the Mack trucks Destroy our dreams of lawyers and actors Keep us spiralin, goin backwards At age nine, saw my first hate crime Blindfolded, expected to walk a straight line Mind molded, taught to love you and hate mine Climbed over it, at a early age, Jay shined Fuck the system at Lady Justice I blaze nine Your Honor, I no longer kill my people, I raise mine The soul of Mumia in this modern day time[MTV] While the jury is inside deliberating outside the crowd is frozen with anticipation[Hook][MTV] Well the verdict has just been announced: NOT GUILTY! It is complete pandemonium out here! [Hook; Serena keeps speaking] People are cheering and hugging - there he is  is exiting the courtroom right now There is a swarm of cameras surrounding him [pop bulbs flashing] and people are just rushing up to him Let's try and make our way over there, ! ![sounds of cameras keep flashing, music fades]    
  - Things That U Do
"Things That U Do"(feat. Mariah Carey)[] Uh-huh, uh Jigga man, uh-huh MC ThatOs right Swizz Beatz Uh, uh, come on[Mariah ()] It's the things that you do That make me feel so... (Come on, inhale, exhale, breathe on it for me) And I don't know the way I feel I can explain (Uh) I love you You thug look at what you make the clubs do (Bounce, bounce) It's the things that you do That make me feel so.. (Exhale breathe on it for me) And I don't know the way I feel I can explain (Yeah) I love you (Uh come on) You thug look at what you make the clubs do[] You know the flow sicka, know Jigga, mo' sicka now right You know what me and Swizz's shit sound like Crazed and demonic, uh without blazin chronic Product of Reaganomics You know that motherfuckin stoop raised me Ringin in da hoops but I was too lazy School made me sick, teachers said I was too crazy Low and behold, it's the new and improved  Let me explain this to you baby I spent nights out, days in Niggaz was blazing, twelve noon where I was raised in I felt caged in but kept roaming Prayed for the Day of Atonement Married to the streets no date of annulment It seems every time it comes up They postpone it So I kept my chrome at the waist Waiting for the omen Savoring the moment and now you know The reason that I flow the way I flow baby[Mariah ()] It's the things that you do (Uh, inhale, exhale, breathe on it) That make me feel so.. And I don't know the way I feel I can explains I love you You thug look at what you make the clubs do (Bounce, shake, bounce, shake) It's the things that you do That make me feel so.. (Uh, exhale, breathe on it for me) And I don't know the way I feel I can explain (Uh) I love you You thug look at what you make the clubs do (Drop, bounce, yo)[] You know I move like an ounce Bottled up like crack That's how I make you bounce like that Defy Webster's words they can't pronounce like that That's why no other rapper got a sound like that Trap, trap of my life Flashback, kill niggaz Rap skills unmatched, Jigga man baby I can't entertain it sometimes I can't explain it God given, gifts of a soul for hard living Far be it from me to question Allah's wisdom Could've been lost in the system Instead I'm involved with the rhythm I dodged prison, came out unscathed from car collisions I know I must be part of some mission Shit I used take it for granted Why they placed me on this planet I would ask myself while writin raps to myself But right there under my nose Was the flow of all flows Not a demon but a rose in the cement, come on[Mariah ()] It's the things that you do That make me feel so.. (Inhale, exhale, breathe on it MC) And I don't know the way I feel I can explain (Uh) I love you You thug look at what you make the clubs do (Bounce, shake, shake it, uh) It's the things that you do That make me feel so.. (Exhale, uh) And I don't know the way I feel I can explain I love you You thug look at what you make the clubs do (Lights out nigga)[] You know I've traveled through zones Homes spazzed like a bad back I came into this game on Jaz's back I jumped off stood on my own two like boom, that's that Yeah I'm here to show and prove Don't matter to me the Garden or flowin on Clue Whatever niggas wanna do - it's alright with me Whether you big or bossy, jig or flossy Dusty or musty, sober or saucy Broker than Todd Bridges, richer than Bill Cosby Forgive me for my arrogance or you still salty? Past on to the next life and you still haunt me I'mma keep doing me unfortunately I make the club rock, make thugs pop guns Make old folks do the bus stop; can't stop son Shit I give you what's hot and what's not, I never knew Y'all (niggas) know (niggas) how (niggas) do[Mariah ()] It's the things that you do that make me feel so.. (Uh, exhale, inhale) And I don't know the way I feel I can explain I love you You thug look at what you make the clubs do (Uh, bounce, shake, what? uh-huh) It's the things that you do that make me feel so.. (Uh-huh, inhale, exhale) And I don't know the way I feel I can explain I love you You thug look at what you make the clubs do (Bounce, shake ladies) It's the things that you do that make me feel so.. (Uh-huh, breathe for me, uh, uh-huh) And I don't know the way I feel I can explain (Uh) I love you You thug look at what you make the clubs do (Lights out niggas) It's the things that you do that make me feel so.. And I don't know the way I feel I can explain I love you You thug look at what you make the clubs do It's the things that you do that make me feel so.. And I don't know the way I feel I can explain I love you You thug look at what you make the clubs do It's the things that you do that make me feel so.. And I don't know the way I feel I can explain I love you You thug look at what you make the clubs do     
  - It's Hot (Some Like It Hot)
"It's Hot (Some Like It Hot)"[] Can't stop it nigga, uh Mm-hmm, uh-huh, can't stop that Timbaland uh-huh.. Jigga Man uh-huh Yeah.. Brook, Brook-Brooklyn huh? That's right Put your motherfuckin hands together, uh-huh Put your motherfuckin hands together Yo, can't stop it Yo.. Yo show closer, J-to-the-A-Y-Hovah Place shutter down, who the fuck'll fuck around? Game spitter, Range sitter, Bentley driver nigga Keep a full clip I have to empty out on niggaz Hoe bagger, no slacker, get this shit jumpin like eight blacks, fo' crackers, get yo' ass jumped Crist' sipper, six dipper, wrist glitter nigga Gat buster, ass toucher.. clit licker Go against Jigga yo' ass is dense I'm about a dollar, what the fuck is 50 Cents? Hot shit, kick a nigga, turn these mics out My jewelry so bright you can turn these lights out Hovah's like Noah keep two in the truck I'm like U-Haul; every bitch move when I fuck You move slut, I gotta put two in your butt I'm everything: the when's, why's, who's, and what Nigga what?[Chorus:  (repeat 2X w/ minor variations)] Hell no you can't stop it, when it's hot it's hot My grind, keep me jumpin out of drop to drop My shine, lose your sight tryin to watch the watch When there's drama Jigga pop, Jigga pop, pop[] Seperate myself from the lame, no you can't see me I'm 6-0-0, you 300 C-E Give my ladies dick, my young hoes pee-pee Hits in a row like MJ; "Hee-hee!" Since I was waist height, late night, bustin in the clouds Runnin wild, comin home late, cussin out my mouth Niggaz said, "Bryan leave your cousin in the house" Everytime we play the Dozen, he's buggin out While y'all was playin yo-yo, I was sittin on low pros Dippin the po-po, gettin that dough-dough No, no I ain't stupid I take loot kid What's in the bank? Shoot it Lose it like I ain't do it You wanna play Jigga nigga what you drank fluid? Got a full tank now you wanna pull rank? I clap still, act ill, Jigga shoot thee Give you chest pains, leg sprains absolutely What?[Chorus][] Thirty-eight revolve like the sun round the Earth Try to play hard get you found round the dirt Six shell casings found round your shirt[cyring] in surround sound from the hearse Jigga Man, trigger man, hit your man up Six shots, hit the pole, hit the van up Kidnap grown folks get them grands up Timbaland, hot shit, get them hands up[Chorus 2X]    
  - Snoopy Track
"Snoopy Track"(feat. Juvenile)[] Bounce Uhhh, ha, uhhh, ha Uhhh, uh-huh-uh-uhhh, uhh, uh-huh This for my hustlers.. uh-huh And for the bitches.. yeah Yo, yo This is for my niggaz down in Houston on candy paint All my niggaz in the Dirty South, Miami mayne All my niggaz in the A-T-L throwin dem bones All them thugs that send slugs through your clothes; holla at me It's for the black culture, Spanish chicks with the sweet chocha Spanish cats with the ki's of cocoa All the haters eat a dick they wanna see you brok-er I hope the heat stroke ya, the misery is over All my deep smokers, I hope the leaf choke ya Hope you'll never be sober I'ma toast to myself I hope the Crist' get me, spiralin into a tizzy So pissy, swervin on the road dizzy May God protect my soul, angels walk with me First do the flow sickly, niggaz is so shifty The fo'-fo' is like a force field, you won't get me I brought some folk with me, Brooklyn is loc'n with me What the fuck?[Chorus: Juvenile repeat 2X] You know, we ride All day, all night Pop Crist, shoot dice Fuck hoes, for life[] This is for my chicks that get dough for takin off they clothes All them money makin honeys that slide down the poles All my educated chicks who grade is 4.0 All the baby mamas across the globe; aiyyo I like my women friends feminine I like my hoes on "X" like Eminem.. shit! I like em bow-legged, never coke-headed With a dough fetish - the drive to go get it I like they toes proper, I like they clothes Prada I like they shoes Gucci, I like new coochie I fucked a few groupies, in a few hoopties I got em iceberg shit they thought I knew Snoopy I cop them Roc-a-Wear, my mamis dedicated They never tell me no, the most they said is "not here" I got they ears studded, both wrists baguetted I got a main chick, a mistress, and a young bitch Forget it I'm the don[Chorus][] Wha-What? This is for my dice shooters, cats doin life By the time I get this kite to ya, I hope you doin alright Who got em platinum up? Who got the chicks in the truck? Too much to sit comfortably, they lappin up Who shit is big pimpin? See the flow different I drop heavy then I let the four-fifth flip em I keep rappers talkin to kids, Jigga "Sixth Sense-d" em Don't mention my name and lames in the same sentence You see I'm so thorough, take on your whole borough Be so careful I hear the whistle from the fo'-fo' barrel Keep the flow Hovah; icy neck, cold shoulder Who click is closest to La Costra Nostra? It's "The Roc"[Chorus 1.5X]    
  - S. Carter
"S. Carter"(feat. Amil)[] S-dot-Carter Y'all must try harder Competition is[Amil] Nada Ladies scream papa Niggas can't stop ya Competition is[] No, no, no S-dot-Carter Y'all must try harder Competition is[Amil] Nada Ladies scream papa Niggas can't stop ya Competition is[] No, no, no, nope You can't see 'em Though you got plans to be him Pay homage if by chance you meet him In his pants pocket, your advance in pedium It's the undisputed champ, being For clique, dough sick, no medicine for us Competition like I said in the chorus Let me spell it out for ya Jay to tha Amil (A to the Y stay real fuck how they feel, uh-huh, uh-huh) That's how we put it down (Uh-huh, uh-huh y'all gon get it now) Chip off the old block Resemble my old pops 'Cept I tote glocks and open dope spots And I shut down rap crews Smack them cats who flash tools Laugh at fake ballers with bad jewels I'll tell you once This is shit you should've of knew (Jigga what?) Jigga (Jigga who?) Okay[] S-dot-Carter Y'all must try harder Competition is[Amil] Nada Ladies scream papa Niggas can't stop ya Competition is[] No, no, no S-dot-Carter Y'all must try harder Competition is[Amil] Nada Ladies scream papa Niggas can't stop ya Competition is[] No, no, no I'mma Roc-a-fella soldier I thought I told ya Hustler, nigga move weight like Oprah Drive wide body, twenty-inch big motor No tints, make no mistake y'all it's Hova I stay sportin' played Jordan's before Jordan Verses tight, hooks harder than Ken Norton Musically touching you Truthfully I abuse beats better call BCW I make my mother move So I have no problem coming around the old way Sluggin' you, that's what a thug will do (Thuggin', bust techs, a suspect dangerous, and I love rough sex) Yeah that's what's up Even when I'm asleep the gats is up Paranoid like Sunny drive backing up But I'm from Bed-Stuy, killa with the flow Let lead fly from out the four-four, motherfuckers[] S-dot-Carter Y'all must try harder Competition is[Amil] Nada Ladies scream papa Niggas can't stop ya Competition is[] No, no, no S-dot-Carter Y'all must try harder Competition is[Amil] Nada Ladies scream papa Niggas can't stop ya Competition is[] No, no, no None I remain at the top like the sun And I burn whoever come in my chambers of torture The flame gon' spark ya Blood stain the tarp But remains they chalk ya Don't try to smooth talk us[Amil ()] You got nothing to offer But the baby nine And make ya fine offer The chick is ill Even with four-inch heels No panties on and Patricia Fields I get down Just name the time, the place We could take it back to Vaseline on our face On a regular day we just gleam up your space Rock our own line, got our whole team laced RW with the torch on my jeans by the waist Without heat we still gon steam up the place (Amil-lion, Jigga man, flawless, here we go)[] S-dot-Carter Y'all must try harder Competition is[Amil] Nada Ladies scream papa Niggas can't stop ya Competition is[] No, no, no S-dot-Carter Y'all must try harder Competition is[Amil] Nada Ladies scream papa Niggas can't stop ya Competition is[] No, no, no     
  - Pop 4 Roc
"Pop 4 Roc"(feat. Amil, Beanie Siegal, Memphis Bleek)[Amil ()] (Alright yeah) Would ya love me? (Uh-huh, alright) Would ya hate me? (Watch this yo) I know ya love me (Alright) I know ya hate me (Uh Clue) Would ya love me? (Brand new Duro) Would ya hate me? I know ya love me (Feel this yo, uh)[Amil] Uh, uh, uh See me comin through hair done just a slinging my shit With something Gucci on clinging to my hips Frontin with the Star Tech ringing in the whip Icy ears, neck, fingers for years Got the show wild with the toes out Shit I don't fuck with no stingy nigga I rock Prada, Chanel, and Fendi nigga What I'mma do with your little blunts and Henney nigga? I'mma Major Coin with a pretty Bentley nigga Uh my niggas will ride for me You should see all the things they buy for me Uh, it's obvious how I spend my time Around ballers all day don't have to spend a dime Callin' up room service when it's dinner time Get my tan on in the tropics in the winter time nigga, uh, uh, uh[Amil (Beanie Siegal)] Would ya love me? (If we couldn't cop the drop) Would ya hate me? (If we couldn't drop the top) I know ya love me (Cuz you know we pop 4 Roc) I know ya hate me (Cuz you know we got shit locked) Would ya love me? (If we couldn't cop the drop) Would ya hate me? (If we couldn't drop the top) I know ya love me (Cuz you know we pop 4 Roc) I know ya hate me (And you know we got shit locked)[Beanie Siegal] Ay yo, we gon' stop this here Get this clear the general of the Roc in here Beanie Siegal hottest thing on the block this year Keep the ego we been bound to the top ya hear Forget about it you don't know me yo stop the stares I've been about it pop you then pop ya peers You know how I do six coup, top be clear You know how I play low layer Roc-A-Wear Catch Siegal in the kitchen balloon in the pie Y'all from whom to buy Y'all niggas know if y'all cross Mac Y'all soon to die Cuz you know I bring heat like June and July Spit like August I'm the truth I'm not lying I'm the reason why Jay feel comfortable retiring I gotta laugh cuz y'all work hard at this shit Think about yo I just started this shit Just imagine if I put my heart in this shit Scary sight y'all niggas feel me right God damn yo I barely write But every rhyme be in check like a pair of Nikes[Amil (Beanie Siegal)] Would ya love me? (If we couldn't cop the drop) Would ya hate me? (If we couldn't drop the top) I know ya love me (Cuz you know we pop 4 roc) I know ya hate me (Cuz you know we got shit locked) Would ya love me? (If we couldn't cop the drop) Would ya hate me? (If we couldn't drop the top) I know ya love me (Cuz you know we pop 4 roc) I know ya hate me (And you know we got shit locked)[Memphis Bleek] Yo, yo, well I'm gold now Memph Man Coming Of Age and I'm grown now Sittin on chrome now I'm the youngest gun, I get it on with anyone I've been in thirty beefs shit I'm barely 21 Guns I hold em like offensive linemen Bring em back to the streets like a brick on consignment Interlining of the Mark Buchanan Spark two hammers Memph Man gold marks the understanding[] We don't engage in war we elope Orange juice style beat niggas to a pulp We broke nigga you just told 3 jokes Me, Biggs, and Dame we get some things See the six dames me and Biggs live in the Range Mine's platinum his Champagne Niggas whisper cuz if they talk they gets slain Y'all's was looking for me on the charts the bricks came Left the same night in the morning the chicks came I just use rap to put shit in my name The death's just a matter of time the hit's been arranged Contracts signed the shits in your name Just to lame rap niggas I'm the king Motherfuck the ring mami kiss the chain I don't got game to waste on y'all I'm don't think with my dick or chase my balls I'm a hustla hit me with an eighth of raw And when I get on top I'mma blaze all y'all Keep em laced some more I know you want some things I drink a lot of water mami come clean Chicks I pump her then dump her Cars we got em bumper to bumper Rap niggas y'all days are numbered Nobody drop nothin' next summer, yeah[Amil (Beanie Siegal)] Would ya love me? (If we couldn't cop the drop) Would ya hate me? (If we couldn't drop the top) I know ya love me (Cuz you know we pop 4 roc) I know ya hate me (Cuz you know we got shit locked) Would ya love me? (If we couldn't cop the drop) Would ya hate me? (If we couldn't drop the top) I know ya love me (Cuz you know we pop 4 roc) I know ya hate me (And you know we got shit locked)[] Yeah R-O-C for the 2 triple O Ya heard me You are about to witness a dynasty like no other Beanie Siegal, The General Amil-lion, Diana Ross of the ROC Memph Bleek, Young god Ha, ha Jigga Man, get ya mind right niggas     
  - Watch Me
"Watch Me"(feat. Dr. Dre)[Dre] YEAH![Jay] Uh uhh uh-uhh, boom boom boom[Dre] D-R-E![Jay] Say it with me niggaz, boom boom[Dre] And ![Jay] Boom boom boom boom[Dre] What the fuck?![Jay] Boom boom boom boom[Dre] Watch me![Jay] Jigga-Man, ya heard? Boom boom boom Brooklyn, ya heard? Boom boom booom[Dre] Compton![Jay] Gotti Gotti ya heard? Yo..[Dre] C'mon![] You gotta, pop that styles, rock that watch dial See that Benz? Cop that now Drop-that-top-down, they gon' kill us anyway Them cops uptown hit holmes with forty-one rounds Live yo' life, get yo' ice She been with you since day one nigga, trick on yo' wife Spend that dough, when in doubt, take that trip She ain't livin for the moment homey shake that bitch He that cool, he can't take you nowhere? Then leave that fool Be that rude if he that cool Save for what? Ball til your days is up This place is fucked, all type of AIDS and such How they make it where you afraid to fuck They gave us drugs then turned around and investigated us Life is short, then you on life support so in between it all I'ma say I seen it all, watch me[Chorus: Dr. Dre] Place yourself in the shoes of true felons (uh-huh) and tell me you won't ball every chance you get (uhh, watch me) At any, chance you hit (that's right) we live for the moment (yo, watch, watch) Makes sense don't it? Now make dollars (Watch me) You see me around some cheese (Watch me) See me with hustlers around them G's (Watch me) Blowin 'dro runnin through pounds of weed (Watch me) At the bar baby, round's on me (Watch me)[] Watch me turn somethin out of nothin, turn platinum from gold Watch me light the Cohiba off the Viking stove I take an empty bank account, fill it with oh's I take an empty building then I fill it with hoes Watch me, cop that Coupe, shine for the ladies have em sayin, "Damn I never seen a watch that blue" And while they still mesmerized I pop that cooch' Shit, law enforcement couldn't stop that dude Guess who? Fresh off of "Volume 2" Back at you, peep the numbers my album do They call me Cham-pagne-hovah, wake up with a hangover When y'all think the game's over, do the same thing over Still with the same soldiers Still gettin brain and it's plain ain't a thang gon' change over Hop out the truck, hand on my cock and nuts Who got the bank, I'm stoppin it up, watch me[Chorus: Dr. Dre] Place yourself in the shoes of true felons (uh-huh) and tell me you won't ball every chance you get (watch me) At any, chance you hit, we live for the moment Makes sense don't it? Now make dollars (Watch me) You see me around some cheese (Watch me) Hangin with hustlers around them G's (Watch me) Blowin 'dro runnin through pounds of weed (Watch me) At the bar bitch, round's on me (Watch me)[] Yo the watch too rocky, need shades Continental sittin on blades, spinnin like waves Gun too Brock-y, behave Big shot, plus I'm feelin like Rocky these days Ice don't melt I could ski through a heatwave Nights won't help you see Jay, it'll be day My shit too bright, I rip through mics plus I push more powder than Crystal Light Chick mad, said I hold my pistol too tight Get a grip bitch, this how I get through life I buy out the bar, spit Crist' through the mic See Jigga in the 6 and all the shit you like See Jigga givin dick to every bitch you like I told her, "It's Jay-Day and Hit-You-Night" You wanna, see me again you gotta get two dice I got rules I can't hit you twice, you heard me? Watch me[Chorus: Dr. Dre] Place yourself in the shoes of true felons (uh-huh) and tell me you won't ball every chance you get (that's right) At any, chance you hit, we live for the moment Makes sense don't it? Now make dollars (Watch me) You see me around some cheese (Watch me) See me with hustlers around them G's (Watch me) Blowin 'dro runnin through pounds of weed (Watch me) At the bar baby, round's on me (Watch me) (Watch me) You see me around some cheese (Watch me) Hangin with hustlers around them G's (Watch me) Blowin 'dro runnin through pounds of weed (Watch me) At the bar bitch, round's on me (Watch me)[] Uh-huh-uh uh-uhh uh-uhh.. uh Uh-huh-uh uh-uhh uh-uhh.. Uh-huh-uh, Jigga Jigga shit huh? Uh-huh, uh-huh-uh, Brooklyn-Brooklyn shit huh? (Compton) Uh-huh-uh, Gotti Gotti shit huh? (C'mon) Uh-huh, uh-huh-uh, Lil' Rob shit huh? (C'mon) Uh-huh-uh-UHH, Roc-a-Fella shit y'all (C'mon) Uh-huh, uh-huh, murder murder shit y'all (Watch me!)     
  - Big Pimpin'
"Big Pimpin'"[] Uhh, uh uh uh It's big pimpin baby.. It's big pimpin, spendin G's Feel me.. uh-huh uhh, uh-huh.. Ge-ge-geyeah, geyeah Ge-ge-geyeah, geyeah.. You know I - thug em, fuck em, love em, leave em Cause I don't fuckin need em Take em out the hood, keep em lookin good But I don't fuckin feed em First time they fuss I'm breezin Talkin bout, "What's the reasons?" I'm a pimp in every sense of the word, bitch Better trust than believe em In the cut where I keep em til I need a nut, til I need to beat the guts Then it's, beep beep and I'm pickin em up Let em play with the dick in the truck Many chicks wanna put Jigga fist in cuffs Divorce him and split his bucks Just because you got good head, I'ma break bread so you can be livin it up? Shit I.. parts with nothin, y'all be frontin Me give my heart to a woman? Not for nothin, never happen I'll be forever mackin Heart cold as assassins, I got no passion I got no patience And I hate waitin.. Hoe get yo' ass in And let's RI-I-I-I-I-IDE.. check em out now RI-I-I-I-I-IDE, yeah And let's RI-I-I-I-I-IDE.. check em out now RI-I-I-I-I-IDE, yeah[Chorus One: ] We doin.. big pimpin, we spendin G's Check em out now Big pimpin, on B.L.A.D.'s We doin.. big pimpin up in N.Y.C. It's just that Jigga Man, Pimp C, and B-U-N B Yo yo yo.. big pimpin, spendin G's We doin - big pimpin, on B.L.A.D.'s We doin.. big pimpin up in N.Y.C. It's just that Jigga Man, Pimp C, and B-U-N B[Bun B] Nigga it's the - big Southern rap impresario Comin straight up out the black bar-rio Makes a mill' up off a sorry hoe Then sit back and peep my sce-nawr-e-oh Oops, my bad, that's my scenario No I can't fuck a scary hoe Now every time, every place, everywhere we go Hoes start pointin - they say, "There he go!" Now these motherfuckers know we carry mo' heat than a little bit We don't pull it out over little shit And if you catch a lick when I spit, then it won't be a little hit Go read a book you illiterate son of a bitch and step up yo' vocab Don't be surprised if yo' hoe stab out with me and you see us comin down on yo' slab Livin ghetto-fabulous, so mad, you just can't take it But nigga if you hatin I then you wait while I get yo' bitch butt-naked, just break it You gotta pay like you weigh wet wit two pairs of clothes on Now get yo' ass to the back as I'm flyin to the track  Timbaland let me spit my pro's on Pump it up in the pro-zone That's the track that we breakin these hoes on Ain't the track that we flow's on But when shit get hot, then the glock start poppin like ozone We keep hoes crunk like Trigger-man Fo' real it don't get no bigger man Don't trip, let's flip, gettin throwed on the flip Gettin blowed with the motherfuckin Jigga Man, fool[Chorus Two: Bun B] We be.. big pimpin, spendin G's We be.. big pimpin, on B.L.A.D.'s We be.. big pimpin down in P.A.T. It's just that Jigga Man, Pimp C, and B-U-N B Cause we be.. big pimpin, spendin G's And we be.. big pimpin, on B.L.A.D.'s Cause we be.. big pimpin in P.A.T. It's just that Jigga Man, Pimp C, and B-U-N B.. nigga[Pimp C] Uhh.. smokin out, throwin up, keepin lean up in my cup All my car got leather and wood, in my hood we call it buck Everybody wanna ball, holla at broads at the mall If he up, watch him fall, nigga I can't fuck witch'all If I wasn't rappin baby, I would still be ridin Mercedes Chromin shinin sippin daily, no rest until whitey pay me Uhhh, now what y'all know bout them Texas boys Comin down in candied toys, smokin weed and talkin noise[Chorus Two]    
  - There's Been A Murder
"There's Been A Murder"[BLAM BLAM][woman screaming in pain.. cops yelling "Go! Go! Go! Go!"][police sirens][Hook:] Think there's been a murder-errra-ahhh-hahh-ahhh I ahh, think there's been a.. I.. I think there's been a.. Think there's been a murder-errra-ahhh-hahh-ahhh I ahh, think there's been a.. I.. I think there's been a..[] I hustle from, night to morning, dawn to dusk Kidnap and robberies like (c'mon nigga) "You're going with us" I held roundtable meetings so we could go on and discuss not only money but all the emotions going through us Why we don't cry when niggas die, that's how the street raised him Look in the air, say a prayer (hail Mary) hoping God forgave him Cop liquor, twist it, tap it twice, pour it to the pavement We live dangerous, often finding ourself in the eyes of strangers (Who the fuck is you?) My dream is big and in it my team is rich as seen through the eyes of a nigga who ain't seen shit Back to live action, I'm packing, I'm still in the mix like new hits, I think I'm going over your head a little bit But I let you know I changed names when I roam through town Stay free and be who I'm professional known as now Jay-motherfucking-Z; and with that said back to Shawn Carter the hustler,  is dead, and uh[Hook][] My infatuation with autos led to autos getting sprayed Houses getting broken in, quarters getting tried Bricks getting chopped, mom's pots getting used One thrown in that water, try the soda in there too Expensive shoes worn, Louis Vuitton seat, roof gone Coke cheap, my face is like a coupon I gotta do Shawn, 'cause even when  was lukewarm I was getting my loot on, nigga I'm too strong Eat till the food's gone, they placed me on this earth The twin brother of Rick Porter, separated at birth I got the soul of a hustler, quiet noise like a muffler Fuck with us, walk through the ghetto, see the place that corrupted us Learn why we buck at the guys that come up with us Ain't enough bucks for us to split in this shit Plus ain't nobody loving us; and with that said back to Shawn Carter the hustler,  is dead, and uh[Hook][] See my life is like a see-saw And until I move this weight it's gonna keep me to the floor Travel with me through my deep thoughts You all can't learn Jigga by the shit you all be reading in The Source; It's deeper of course Follow the life of this reckless minor At sixteen in the 600, unlicensed driver Playing, cops and robbers, like shots can't stop us Flipping a bird to the choppers (fuck you coppers) Buck-thirty on the turns Reckless abandon, when I'm standing on this pedal Hand on my metal, minus all this time they trying to give me Lord help me, all I ever wanted to be was wealthy or somebody to tell me that they felt me I tried to play the hand you dealt me but you gave me five funnies and shit I was hungry I need menage money Nothing less than a 520; and with that said back to Shawn Carter the hustler,  is *BLAM* (Think there's been a murder-errra-ahhh-hahh-ahhh)  
  - Come And Get Me
"Come And Get Me"[] I remove your roof nigga let the sun shine in Thirty-eight waist, enough to put one nine in Really a thirty-six without the gun I'm thin but when the gat is tucked, I'm fat as fuck Ignorant bastard, I'm takin it back to day one No kids, but trust me I know how to raise a gun For niggaz that think I spend my days in the sun well here's the shock of your life, the glock not the mic Homey I'm not into hype; trust me, I'm still street You still fuckin up then trust me I still creep Yeah I know the platinum chain be lookin real sweet but reach and I bury niggaz sixty feet deep S dot Carter turn rappers into martyrs Seperate fathers from they daughters, why bother I'm a crook like you, I took like you I disobeyed the law threw out the book like you How dare you look at Jigga like I'm shook like boo I keep the fifth with me nigga, come and get me.. COME AND GET ME![gong sounds] Ka-ka-ka-ka-ka-ka-ka-come..[bell rings] COME AND GET ME! Ka-ka-ka-COME AND GET ME! ..[bell rings] COME AND GET ME! Ka-ka-ka..[bell rings] .. Ka-ka-ka-ka-come[bell rings] .. come and get me COME AND GET ME[] Don't know what y'all niggaz is tryin to do but I don't like it Yeah, straight gangster shit Heyyyy, uh-huh-uh-uhh gangster shit Uhh, straight gangster nigga Roc.. Yo, your summer's bout to get hot Niggaz home from jail and they plottin Heard about the watch, the Bentley hard-top The Continental T, got em resentin me God I work hard, please don't envy me I paid the cost to be the boss to floss this hard I can recall a year ago I almost lost this job All y'all remember is the part about me parkin the hog What about all them days I was walkin my dogs? Barkin at broads, but they never hollered back And if they did all they said was, "Where dem dollaz at?" Imagine, bein skinny growin up around broader cats The quiet assassin demeanor of them college cats until I got a gat and loudly start poppin back Round the way, niggaz called me Bobby Bouchete Now all I hear is whispers of what you gon' do to Jay How y'all gon' stick me up, take my jewels away Pull out your gat, car jack me take my cruise away Well I got news for y'all fools today, hey..[Chorus: ] I got, shots to give come and get me nigga Y'all wanna rob the kid? Come and get me nigga I won't, part with this come and get me nigga I worked, hard for this come and get me nigga I got, shots to give, COME AND GET ME.. COME AND GET ME..[] I made it so, you could say Marcy and it was all good I ain't crossover I brought the suburbs to the hood Made em relate to your struggle, told em bout your hustle Went on MTV with do-rags, I made them love you You know normally them people wouldn't be fuckin witchu Til I made em understand why you do what you do I expected to hear, "Jay, if it wasn't for you.." But instead, all I hear is buzzin in your crew How y'all scheamin, tryin to get accustomed to my moves So y'all could tape my mouth, stake out my house But I got pride I'm a nigga first I gotta cock back and pull the trigger first That's how Jigga work The funny thing; I represent y'all everytime I spit a verse and that's the shit that hurts But hey, I got my mind right, got my nine right here So when y'all feel that the time is right..[Chorus][] Aiy yo yo, aiy yo yo It's only fair that I warn ya, rap's my new hustle I'm treatin it like the corner, fuck with me if you wanna My game change but my mindframe remains the same I gotta protect what's mine Shit I started from nothin; zero, zip I made my way hustlin, I don't owe niggaz shit I'm paranoid now, so I keep the gun gripped Cats I played skelly with? Niggaz done flipped I keep a banger in the ankle, one in the hip Two in the stash, one come up when I shift I keep one under the chair where I sit I even got a gun in the hair in the bun of my bitch Ask Big; everytime he'd come to my crib he'd find another gun that I hid I'm ready to make this one of the, hottest summer there is Everyday like a hundred-and-six.. shit..[Chorus 2X][] Motherfuckers!     
  - NYMP
"NYMP"[] Geyeah, NYMP the realest, uhh This is educated thug MU-SIC, niggaz Life's a battle, mean streets eat you alive Blocks'll have you, tryin to maintain your course through the potholes and gravel Hot holes and what-have-you, tryin to clock dough Foes tryin to pop shots through you by code Pigs tryin to grab you and lock up your soul Through the Hot Apple, nighttime shots crackle (bucka bucka bucka) Fiends tryin to gaffle you Not only cokeheads but the Feds in the Mercuray Topaz after you, up the avenue Tryin to give you big numbers, you got math to do Tryin to make you miss summer, shit, that ain't cool I caught smaller cases tryin to get cap or two Up against the wall, tryin to pass through Ghost-like, hear the cries from the tortured souls Most nights, I hold my toast tight, and it goes like[Chorus: ] N.Y.M.P., the realest niggaz N.Y.M.P., the realest niggaz Uhh, uh-huh-uh-UHH, N.Y.M.P. the realest Marcy.. Brooklyn..[] Yo; I come through, gettin money, sittin on twenties Niggaz throwin me shade, but ain't shit sunny Hot shells only thing niggaz could get from me Cocktails thrown in your living room, KA-BOOM I'm so confrontational; they shoulda never let me go on probation yo I'm a hustler; except that.. no correctional facilities can correct that I took a step back, I viewed myself, seen where my head was at It's where that dough is homey, gotta get that Gotta get away, some try but head back Uhh, street smart niggaz got left back Some died, they left stacks Me, I ball right, and on top of that I'm dog nice Jigga been cold as fuck before ice Not before Christ, but a long fuckin time Get your mind right niggaz[Chorus: ] N.Y.M.P., the realest Uh-huh-uh-UHH, N.Y.M.P., the realest niggaz Uhh uh-huh, uh-UHH, N.Y.M.P. the realest niggaz Marcy.. feel me..[] I looked Death in the face years back I held tears back, I gathered myself and stared back I'm from where you don't crack, the weak don't live You gotta bounce back homey, the streets don't give I take and rape villages, who gon' stop him? Not Rudy Guiliani, not Hillary Rodham Still I still pop him Shit I grassy knoll and hilltop him, it's all political now I think big when I spit at you now Between my dog and the figures, the four gonna get'cha Between life and death, they killed my spirit So what little life I got left, y'all can expect me to ball I ? myself, teacher said I was a lost cause cause I used to roam them halls Still I spit knowledge, dropped out of high school, skipped college Who woulda thought I'd make it "Big" like Ms. Wallace?[Chorus: ] Uhh, yeah, N.Y.M.P., the realest niggaz Brooklyn, what? N.Y.M.P., the realest niggaz Uhh, uh-huh-uh-UHH, N.Y.M.P. the realest niggaz Marcy.. Brooklyn, N.Y.M.P. the realest, feel me[] Educated, thug mu-sic niggaz This is Brooklyn, this is gangsta, this is project Real shit, N.Y.M.P. the realest niggaz Marcy, Brooklyn, stompin grounds Fuck with me     
